What's that mean?
[ Gunshot ]
♪♪ [ Alternative Rock:
"Sea Lion" ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
Mr. Addy,
your dissertation
is entitled...
"Analysis of Bone Trauma."
When viewed in cross section,
the pressure and force...
exerted by the weapon
can be assessed.
Obtaining the cross section
will compromise
the original bone.
My technique preserves
bone surface morphology...
through the use
of polyvinyl replication.
A transparent positive is made
by covering the impression...
with an aqueous solution
of synthetic polymer.
Hey, Bones. Come on.
We got a body.
Went up like a Roman candle.
- Hey, Zack. How's it going?
- So far, they don't like me.
- Shocker. Let's go.
- [ Brennan ] I'm in
the middle of something.
You know, real-life murder
and mutilation versus
academic claptrap, no contest.
- Sorry. No offense.
- This committee can carry on
without you, Dr. Brennan.
Zack, just answer
the questions.
[ Booth ] Yeah.
[ Booth ]
Okay, come on.
Next question?
How do you expect anyone
to take you seriously...
as a working forensic
anthropologist...
when you look
the way you do?
What?
[ Brennan ]
Male, middle-aged.
What was with Zack back there?
Defending his dissertation.
Last step before
he gets his doctorate.
I think these
are what's left
of his intestines.
Is he gonna make it?
No. He's very dead.
[ Chuckles ]
I mean Zack.
Ah, 50-50.
He's a stoolie.
Zack?
Our victim.
No, he's a rat, a snitch.
What makes you say that?
His guts got spilled.
You know, spill your guts.
Very literal.
Hung up there like a scarecrow
on a rooftop of a hotel used to
house witnesses. It's a warning.
There's something jammed
down his trachea.
[ Zack ] I rectified their
erroneous assumptions concerning
polyvinyl replication.
You corrected them?
Only when they were wrong.
[ Chuckles ]
Are the remains
ready for X-ray?
Yes. Maybe
we'll get lucky and I.D.
the poor bastard that way.
Oh, we just got lucky.
"My name is Garrett Delaney."
There's something
metallic here.
This is gonna turn out
to be some freaky, weird
ritualistic thing, isn't it?
Oh, man, I hope so.
Christopher Columbus.
- Where's Dr. Brennan?
- Her brother came for a visit.
Dad called you?
You're sure it was him?
He said, "You and your sister
are in danger," and he hung up.
I spend half my time
with a sniper-trained
F.B.I. agent. I feel safe.
Tempe, I know someone
is watching me.
What's your evidence?
I can feel it
on the back of my neck.
You spend some time in jail,
you develop a sixth sense.
Maybe you should stay
with me for a few days.
Tempe, I have work.
- I have Amy and the girls.
- What about your sixth sense?
- Hey!
- What?
You can't not believe
in something one second,
and then use it
against me in the next.
It's a long drive.
You could start fresh tomorrow.
And I've got...
cold beer in the fridge.
Don't drink the Moroccan beer.
Tastes like ear wax.
How you doing, Russell?
Okay, Booth.
You? Good?
Yeah. Good.
I still make him nervous,
don't I? Come on. Let's go.
Why do I always feel
like you're abducting me?
[ Booth ]
Yeah. It turns out our corpse
is a former F.B.I. agent.
Garrett Delaney,
he left the F.B.I.
about 15 years ago.
He's now head of security of
some big K Street lobbyist.
So why'd he end up
a human torch?
That's what we're here
to find out.
His place is much
better than yours.
Ten times better.
I told you
he left public service.
He makes, uh,
more money than I.
So that's all
your dad said, huh?
Is you're in danger?
Yes.
- And Russ's sixth sense agrees.
- What are you doing?
I've been practicing some
of the black ops stuff
you taught me.
Let me show you.
Every F.B.I. agent
in the country is
looking for my father.
Maybe he's trying
to scare us off.
Six months without
a break in the case,
he ain't gonna be nervous.
Now let me show you.
My dad's a career criminal.
Just because he says
that Russ is in danger
doesn't mean it's the truth.
Let me show you
how it's done, okay?
[ Kicks Door ]
Oh. He might've
gotten it right this time.
Russ.
These are all pictures
of Russ.
♪ ♪
You gotta Frank it up
Frank it up!
Yeah!
It's the perfect blend of
flavor and heat
I put that $#!t on everything
With sonic stupid five many you get to
delicious things are only five bucks
which is helpful yes with making the
sonic to dollar menu sonic or biggest
sale of twenty twenty to go to the
athletics dot com and get to for twenty
four dollar bottom up to eighty percent
of everything and brand new activewear
style in the the classics inspired
college been pregnant at the best
prices every you know that feeling when
it's four am and you're changing a wet
diaper for the bird night in a row I
couldn't take it any more than a found
coterie and it was love at first
overnight is a twelve hour day parade
gets the job done.
[music playing]
Today, you can give
a gift like no other,
a gift that can help St.
Jude Children's Research
Hospital save lives.
I think it's the
most worthwhile place
to put your money when it
comes to childhood cancer.
If it weren't for St. Jude, I
wouldn't be sitting here today.
If it weren't for St.
Jude, a lot of kids
wouldn't be with their
families every day.
Let's come together to help
the children of St. Jude fight
childhood cancer.
Visit this website,
call this number,
or scan the QR code with
your $19 monthly donation.
Join with your debit or
credit card right now,
and we'll send you this St.
Jude t-shirt you can proudly
wear to show your support.
Today, you can help
St. Jude save lives.
It takes a heart
for somebody to say
I have this extra that I'm
willing to give to St. Jude
so that they can
help save more lives.
Make your monthly donation today
to help cure childhood cancer
everywhere.
Get top dollar and sell your home fast
with the very best real estate agents
at ideal agent we thoroughly researched
top agents in your local market we
analyze the results we personally
interviewed them negotiate a great
commission on your behalf as low as two
percent we made the home sewing spirits
simple and easy while saving you
thousands in commissions we saved just
shy of nineteen thousand dollars by
using ideal age I think the be to call
ideal agent somebody who's already bed
and the agents and have somebody that
is top notch the whole lot of work in a
whole lot of worry we've helped
thousands of home sellers a empires get
five-star results breaking as number
one in real estate on trustpilot there's
no obligation or from costs in our
services free and available nationwide
call today or visit ideal agent dot com
the best agents at a great commission
guaranteed.
[school bells]
When pain says, “I'm here,”
I say, “So are they.”
♪♪
ALEVE
- Who do you take it
for?
Of annoying spam texts.
Introducing text killer the new app that
eliminates ninety nine percent of
unwanted tax so you can live your life
spam text grey.
Be ready for whatever life
throws your way.
Only Dial provides a
hard-working clean
but is gentle to skin with
its Skin Smart complex
and 3 moisturizers
to leave your skin feeling
fresh and healthy.
Nothing cleans like Dial.
When you buy a car and drive time we
give you flexible financing super
flexible you adjusted the terms because
if you're in control oh cool we can
change a down payment to exactly what
fits our budget and you can easily see
your monthly payment change to face
numbers check out to drive the car on
your terms about this couch.
Saddled with so much credit card debt
right now the an upgrade car rolls all
my monthly purchasing one easiest on the
lowest I can avoid stuff like that
walker do I sign up get europe great it
upgrade dot.
Me at work, me and Amy.
This was the day
before yesterday.
Dad was right.
Somebody's watching.
- This is worse than watching.
- What do you mean?
- This is hunting.
- Hunting?
As in kill.
You see these?
Right here. These are ranges.
He's picking out a spot
from which to shoot at you.
- So what do I do now?
- The hunter's dead.
The hunt is over, right?
Anyone else
know you're here?
Only Amy.
Great. Call Amy
and tell her if anyone
calls looking for you,
she doesn't know
where you're at.
You should stay with me until
we find out why Delaney
intended to kill you.
- How are you gonna do that?
- By figuring out
who killed him.
[ Angela ]
This is the paper that was
pulled from Delaney's throat.
It was dated, signed,
and initialed at the bottom
of both sides of the page.
February 1978.
It looks like
a cop's notebook.
That makes sense except,
[ Typing ]
"I will not put an innocent man
in prison just because
he is a political threat.
Marvin Beckett hasn't
broken any law."
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Marvin Beckett?
Back in the '60s, Marvin Beckett
was a civil rights activist.
He made his bones protesting...
African American
overrepresentation
in the Vietnam War.
In '78, he was sent
to prison for life.
Why?
He killed an F.B.I. agent
named Gus Harper.
Wait. Augustus Harper?
Yeah. You know the case?
"August Harp."
Look. Augustus Harper.
Oh, wow.
This means Delaney's murder
has something to do...
with Marvin Beckett
going to prison.
Oh, when you're good,
you are very, very good.
1970s, Ohio.
There is a task force made up
of F.B.I., state police,
and local cops.
It goes bad. Starts taking a cut
from the same bank robbers
they're supposed to be catching.
Then they conspire to plan
a stack of stolen money
on Marvin Beckett.
Well, then this young agent,
right, Harper, okay?
He decides he can't live
with that and decides
to blow the whistle.
I can read.
The same guy who's gonna blow
the whistle on them...
for framing Marvin Beckett
then gets murdered
by Marvin Beckett?
Come on. Talk about
killing two birds
with one stone.
Who else knows about this?
Us and you. That's it.
Let's keep it that way.
Hey, I've seen this movie.
I get killed
on the way home.
Then don't go home.
[ Chuckles ]
You serious?
Thirty years ago,
I was married to Gus Harper
for exactly eight months.
I'm not sure
I can help you.
What about the contents
of the note?
What do you people want?
The truth.
The last time the F.B.I.
came to talk to me,
they told me to keep
my mouth shut,
or you won't get your
husband's death benefits.
Your husband is a good man.
And he tried to do
the right thing.
And he ended up dead.
I can't let that stand.
The F.B.I.
murdered Gus.
Then they had
a state funeral for him,
complete with
the grieving widow
as a centerpiece.
Is this your husband's
handwriting?
Yes.
He was compiling evidence.
And there was more?
There was a diary,
a dozen audiotapes,
field notes.
- And where did Gus keep it?
- Safety-deposit box.
Can you tell us where
that safety-deposit box was?
Ohio First Savings and Loan
in Dayton.
Excuse me one moment.
Me.
My parents robbed
that exact bank...
just days after
Gus Harper was killed.
They were looking
for that evidence.
That has to be why Delaney
was stalking Russ.
Go home.
I have a few more questions
for Barbara Harper, okay?
You go home and you be
with your brother, all right?
Okay.
You think it's Delaney?
[ Zack ]
Definitely.
I hope to keep working here
when I receive my doctorate.
We'd all like that.
What did she mean when she said,
"How do you expect anyone
to take you seriously?"
It's a comment on...
your deportment.
Dr. Brennan doesn't
care about deportment.
That's true.
But if you work here,
you won't be Brennan's
grad student anymore.
You'll be a full-blown
forensic anthropologist.
Cam will be your boss.
In your opinion, does
deportment matter to Cam?
Let's just say that Cam's not
the kind of woman you catch...
with crusties
in the corner of her eye.
Haley's six,
and Emma's eight.
Tempe?
I'm sorry.
Preoccupied.
Tempe, if I play
my cards right,
these little girls
are gonna be your nieces
in the next couple months.
The least you can do
is memorize their names.
- They're cute.
- Haley has lung trouble.
They're trying to figure it out.
You ever deal with an H.M.O.?
If it's money, Russ,
I can help.
No, forget it.
If I'm gonna become
these little girls' daddy,
I gotta man up for the job.
[ Knocking ]
That's not rational.
I'm a good mechanic.
I'll take care of my own.
Gus Harper's
service history. Okay?
Graduated top half of his class
in Quantico.
He was assigned to the Joint
State-Federal Bank Robbery
Task Force. Right there.
-The victim.
-Back when he was Special Agent
Delaney supervising Gus Harper.
The guy that was hunting me?
That's right.
Okay, here's a list
of the bank robbers
with their F.B.I. code names.
[ Brennan ]
Dad's code name was Columbus.
Yeah. Lewis, Clark,
Magellan, Cook, Columbus.
All named after explorers.
That's Mom and Dad.
- Every one of these people
are deceased.
- Except for Dad.
Delaney was killed to send
a message to the F.B.I.
This Columbus coin was found
in the victim's mouth.
Columbus shot a man
in the head,
hung him from a pole,
gutted him,
and set him on fire.
And Columbus is our father.
Cfl in miami.
See what you think we just had our
killer and evidence.
U S I miami twelve one central an ion.
♪ ♪
You gotta Frank it up
Frank it up!
Yeah!
It's the perfect blend of
flavor and heat
I put that $#!t on everything
♪♪
I'm not leaving
without these diamonds!
Diamonds?
I'm just here for the stains.
With Persil ProClean.
BOOM.
It's more than Clean.
It's Persil ProClean.
(inspiring music)
- [Graduate] I got my degree
at SNHU for my family.
- [Graduate 1] This
degree is for me.
- [Graduate 2] I did
this for my partner.
- [Graduate 3] My siblings.
- [Graduate 4] My daughter.
- [Graduate 5] My son.
- Congratulations, dad.
- All right.
- [Announcer] No matter who
you get your degree for,
Southern New Hampshire
University can help
you get it done.
With low online tuition and
multiple term starts per year.
So the best time to get
started is right now.
Visit snhu.edu.
♪ If you know, you know ♪
♪♪
Crispy corners.
Sauce on top.
♪♪
♪ If you know, you know ♪
Detroit-Style is back
at Pizza Hut.
Just $12.99.
You are trouble.
You are.
No One OutPizzas The Hut.
[school bells]
When pain says, “I'm here,”
I say, “So are they.”
♪♪
ALEVE
- Who do you take it
for?
Say what are you doing just playing
solitaire oh jane it's not the nineties
anymore.
Grand arbiter has everything you love
about the nostalgic solitaire so much
more exciting is rewarding harvest
feeling and even build your own join
any or newer will just sounded care
download solitaire grand horvitz
between now if you're a medicare
beneficiary in the area cold out to see
how this little card could use a big
benefits including money headed back to
your social security check with one toll
free call you can find out how easy it
is to get all of your original medicare
coverage blush extra benefits you get
an old and one plan designed to fit your
needs so you can be your best every day
you could have medical coverage
prescription drugs with zero dollar
generics dental vision and hearing plus
the world your visa flex card money for
over the counter items and buddy bag and
your social security check each month
and so much more and more good news you
can get a welker plan zero dollar
monthly premium all good well your offer
all of those benefits for zero dollar
monthly premium it's simple medicare
advantage and medicare part D
prescription drug coverage or important
parts of medicare wheelchair has a
contract with medicare to offer and
provide these important options.
Call right now to get your free copy of
the welker all in one guy and call one
eight six six seven four zero four nine
three seven know there was absolutely
no obligation for requesting this free
information.
Offers benefits that go beyond the
basics including money added to your
social security jug to help cover your
part the previous.
Call today to get your free copy of the
all-in-one guide with absolutely no
obligation your free bled guide will
give you the details you need to make a
smart choice medicare coverage just call
one eight six six seven four zero four
nine three seven remember there is no
obligation for requesting this free
information so call a one eight six six
seven four zero four nine three seven
well care of call today.
You plan the perfect thank you with a
promotional product experts at for
impact who attended to every detail did
you get it right.
You certainly dead for the right
products pretty perfect you go to for
imprint dot com for imprint for certain.
[ Russ ]
Dad had it under control.
- I mean, for 15 years,
everything was fine until--
- Until what?
Dad left you a message.
He said, "Stop looking."
You didn't.
So this is my fault?
Well, consequences
aren't the same as fault.
My parole officer
is very philosophical.
Well, all we have is
a voice tape of Dad saying,
"Back off,"
and a little silver dolphin
that I found at Mom's grave.
That's as far as
the investigation has gone.
- According to Booth.
- What? Booth and I
are partners.
Tempe, he's F.B.I.
You aren't.
You're the daughter
of a career criminal and
the sister of a loser on parole.
What?
I wouldn't let anyone else
call you a loser, Russ.
What makes you think
you're allowed?
I love you too.
What you're asking
is the kind of thing
that destroys careers.
From the time I was
a little girl, I dreamed
of putting bad men in jail.
Put that back. Which is why
I became an Assistant
United States Attorney.
You don't have to help me.
Of course
I have to help you!
Marvin Beckett is still a hero
to a lot of African Americans.
Some of us never believed
he killed this F.B.I. boy.
Now you buy me breakfast,
tell me you found a way
to clear his name,
release him out
of wrongful incarceration
after 30 years?
I cannot walk away,
which you already know!
- Maybe you should have
some more coffee.
- Of course I want more coffee.
- We have to come up
with our plan of attack.
- I was thinking Judge Moran--
We should exhume Gus Harper.
See if your genius
scientist partner...
can ascertain whether he died
in the manner the F.B.I.
said he died 30 years ago.
- Moran's got a long--
- No. We want Kemper.
- "Hang 'em High" Kemper?
- I'm ruining my career, I'm
doing it my way, understand?
Now, take a doughnut hole.
I'm offering.
Thanks.
This was lodged in Garrett
Delaney's sinus cavity.
.22 caliber.
These dimples indicate
that the bullet ricocheted
around inside the cranium.
Are you worried
about your doctorate?
No. Dr. Grayson touched me
with an open hand
on the shoulder.
You mean inappropriately?
No. I read a book
on body language.
Apparently in our culture,
when an older male lays
an open hand on a younger male,
it conveys approval.
But if he bumps younger
male with a closed fist,
it conveys doubt.
Dr. Grayson went like this,
not like this.
Like this.
Not like this.
Dr. Grayson is elderly
and arthritic.
Perhaps he simply needed help
getting to his feet like this.
Dr. Brennan,
visitors in your office.
Tempe, this is a friend
of Dad's.
Father Coulter is Toby Coulter,
train trestle guy.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that story.
When Dad and his friend
accidentally blew up
a train trestle.
Come on. How do you
accidentally blow up
a train trestle?
While we.
Well, we were hired by a farmer
to dynamite the ice
off his stock pond.
We get this competition
going who's gonna
slide the dynamite...
farther across the ice
before it blows.
You know it's a federal offense
to blow up a train trestle,
Father.
I mean, even if it is
accidental.
Father Toby Coulter,
meet my partner, Seeley Booth.
- Careful. He's F.B.I.
- Ooh. Well, I'm innocent.
It was Max's toss that brought
the trestle down.
Max Keenan's best friend
grows up to be a priest.
I'm sure your people have
that fact on file somewhere.
Tempe, Father Coulter
has a message from Dad.
It's a private message.
Come to my office.
She's just gonna
tell Agent Booth anyway.
Might as well let him listen.
"Back off."
That's the message.
He said you'd understand.
[ Booth ]
Where'd you see him?
In confession.
We're not Catholic.
Oh, the sanctity
of the confessional
is extended to all.
Um, did he ever call you
on your cell phone, Father?
Two days ago.
- Can I see your phone?
- You want to trace the call?
Yeah.
So, uh, Max Keenan,
he come to you for absolution?
Well, I'm sure you know
the requirements for confession.
Contrition and intent
not to repeat the sin.
And Max doesn't have either.
And as a priest, I failed him.
I never was able to get him
to walk the straight and narrow.
Is there anything else
you can tell us?
Well, he was angry.
He felt his hand
had been forced.
Where can we reach you,
Father?
Father Coulter's staying
at St. Augustine Seminary...
for the next few days
before heading back to Ohio.
Here, Father.
Your father loves you.
Is that part
of Dad's message?
That's a personal
observation.
[ Booth ]
Delaney's murder,
the threats on Russ's life,
this is all happening now
because of a little
metal dolphin...
we found on
your mother's grave.
F.B.I. field unit in Denver
traced it to a local artist
in Mead, Colorado.
Who identified Dad
as the buyer.
But Delaney left the F.B.I.
15 years ago.
And somebody told him
about your dad.
And didn't tell you?
They're part of the conspiracy.
You must be annoyed.
You know what? I am.
And I don't like finding out...
there's a dirty F.B.I. agent
in this building.
Here's what I think happened.
Delaney goes to your father.
He asks him to hand over
the evidence.
He doesn't do it,
he kills you or Russ.
Dad calls Russ to warn him.
And then kills Delaney.
Guts him, burns him,
leaves a calling card.
Don't mess with
Max Keenan's kids.
Am I supposed to like that?
No, Bones. I'll take a stand-up
crook over a crooked cop
any day of the week.
Booth, I got us a meet
with the judge. Let's go.
And you better get back
to your lab in case
we're successful.
I just find it best
to do what she says.
Okay.
You want to exhume
the young F.B.I. agent
that Marvin Beckett murdered?
That's correct,
Your Honor.
- That is a big, noisy mess
in the making.
- [ Door Opens ]
The F.B.I. has credible evidence
that the homicide case against
Marvin Beckett was manufactured.
Assistant United States
Attorney Dan Burridge arguing
against this writ, Judge Kemper.
- On behalf of--
- The F.B.I.
- I thought you were F.B.I.?
- I am, Your Honor.
I told you.
A big, noisy mess.
All right.
Let's hear your argument,
Mr. Burridge.
This is a precipitant exhumation
in a highly inflammatory case.
The evidence to which
Miss Julian alludes
has not been authenticated.
It has been authenticated
by the Jeffersonian Institution.
The F.B.I. would like to do
their own in-house analysis
before proceeding.
Of course they would.
They're the ones who did
the framing 30 years ago.
I take exception to that.
Why? You weren't even
born 30 years ago.
- Judge--
- Not like me
and Judge Kemper...
who got to see firsthand what
Marvin Beckett was really like.
Miss Julian, did you bring
this to me because I knew
Marvin Beckett personally?
Did you? I wasn't aware
of that, Your Honor.
Were you aware of that,
Agent Booth?
We'd like to do this slowly
and carefully, Judge.
That's all.
And we want to exhume Gus Harper
so we can make sure...
he was murdered in exactly
the way the damn F.B.I....
said he was murdered,
Your Honor.
[ Saroyan ] As mandated
by the writ of exhumation
by Judge Theodore Kemper...
of the D.C. Federal
Judicial District,
I, Dr. Camille Saroyan,
will be performing an autopsy...
of Special Agent
Augustus Donald Harper...
under the auspices of
the Jeffersonian Institution.
Date of death:
June 25, 1978.
Date of internment:
July 2, 1978.
Date of exhumation:
that would be today.
Also present
at the post-exhumation autopsy
is Dr. Temperance Brennan.
The original autopsy in 1978
found that Agent Harper...
was killed when he was shot
three times at close range...
by a .38 Colt Detective
Special revolver.
Two shots to the chest,
one piercing the heart.
The other, the left lung.
The third, a shot
to the frontal bone.
- What?
- That bullet hole in the head,
that's from a .38.
- Just like the coroner said.
- I can already tell
these two holes...
are from something
a whole lot bigger than
a snub-nosed revolver.
Something more like a rifle
that a sniper would use.
Zack, you'd better get
a full set of X-rays
before Dr. Saroyan reopens.
We're gonna conduct this one
like the whole world
is watching.
Hey, Russ.
Okay, I'm here.
What's up?
You know,
you're an idiot, Russ.
I like you,
but you're a real idiot.
What'd I do?
I got a call from
your parole officer today.
Why?
Why? Because you crossed
state lines without
informing him.
I just told him you were aiding
in an F.B.I. investigation.
Thanks.
You're slipping,
aren't ya?
Look, I want to marry Amy
and raise her kids.
One of them is sick.
That costs money.
I'm a felon on parole.
I work part-time as a mechanic.
You tell me what job am I gonna
get that lets me be the man
I need to be to raise a family?
You got this sick little girl
depending on you. I get that.
But you go back inside
and you cross that line,
you're not helping anyone out.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Woman Screams ]
Everybody down!
[ People Shouting,
Gasping ]
Where R P proof then period proof and
sweatproof their leak-proof underwear
from next comfy and confident protection
that field just like normal for so many
styles and colors to choose from
switching is easy at next dot.
[ Melissa ]
You hear about cancer.
I just was afraid
that I would lose my son.
You think, why us?
Eyes.
You know, why me?
Why my child?
[ Marlo Thomas ] You can
join the battle to save lives
by supporting St. Jude
Children's Research Hospital.
It is such a gift to give hope
back to a family.
As a dad,
I'm eternally grateful.
[ Non-English speech ]
Pronounce in front of me is.
[ Marlo Thomas ] Join St. Jude
with your debit or credit card
for only $19 a month,
and we'll send you
this St. Jude T-shirt.
St. Jude is only possible
because of the people
who donate.
You're saving children's lives.
You're keeping families together
during the hardest thing
they've ever faced.
[ Marlo Thomas ] Please call
or go online right now
and become
a St. Jude partner in hope.
Hi I'm jeff I'm not stop call when my
grandfather started this business he
relied on freshness quality variety and
service still deliver the fresh or
dried fruits snacks and sweets the
family's all around the country dot com
enjoy free shipping on the first store.
Sit at of annoying spam texts
introducing text killer the new app
that eliminates ninety nine percent of
unwanted tax so you can live your life
spam text.
[school bells]
When pain says, “I'm here,”
I say, “So are they.”
♪♪
ALEVE
- Who do you take it
for?
Do you use viagra or cialis have you
been thinking about trying viagra or
cialis what if we could promise you the
same results for less than three
dollars appeal if you're paying twenty
dollars a pill for viagra you're
getting taken to the cleaners our appeal
delivers the exam the same results for
less than three dollars will do the math
for you you save more than sixteen
dollars a pill for the same results want
more will give you forty blue pills or
forty yellow pills for ninety nine
dollars an ad for more pills free you
save more than five hundred dollars you
don't have to be a rocket scientist to
know what to do next you need to call us
right now now and get your forty four
pills for just ninety nine dollars stop
overpaying for viagra call us and
started saving a ton of money for the
exact same results ordering is fast and
easy with your pills delivered to your
door in an unmarked package golos right
now eight hundred six zero one zero
forty three five eight hundred and six
zero one zero forty three five dad's
meet hundred and six zero one zero
forty three five.
♪♪
I'm not leaving
without these diamonds!
Diamonds?
I'm just here for the stains.
With Persil ProClean.
BOOM.
It's more than Clean.
It's Persil ProClean.
Guys got hair loss I know what you're
thinking should I shaved my head
coleman over wear a hat just stop this
isn't nineteen seventy keep your hair
and your confidence because bosley
america's number one hair restoration
experts can give you your real hair back
permanently check them out because
they're giving away and absolutely free
information kit and a free gift card to
everyone who's gay and this qr code to
do you don't have to look like your dad
because this isn't your dad's hair loss
treatment people all over the country
trust possibly because they're ahead of
the curve they use the latest
technology to give you your real hair
back and the best part bosley permanent
solution is protected by the falsely
guarantee let them show you you for
free how awesome your hair could look
with an absolutely free information kid
and a gift card for two hundred and
fifty dollars off scan the qr code
don't wait scan the code now and ask
about the basel iii guarantee.
Jan really I do to sell.
That we should ever schedule.
There's notice.
Made this hi I'm already thought a
personal loan or credit karma and saw
rates in local laws before I applaud.
Total rovers coming tomorrow couldn't
get those roofers come today huh I find
alone up to fifty thousand dollars on
credit karma.
[ Woman On TV ] Civil rights
activist and convicted
murderer Marvin Beckett...
was released today
when a second autopsy...
on his alleged victim,
F.B.I. Agent Gus Harper,
revealed inconsistencies
with details of Mr. Beckett's
trial back in 1979.
[ Coulter ]
What kind
of inconsistencies?
All you know.
You have your confidences
to keep, Father.
I have mine.
Well, it's over, right?
I mean, now that it's out,
there's no reason to kill Russ.
You know, the men behind this,
they don't care
about Marvin Beckett.
They care
about being exposed.
Lucky you were together.
Why were you together?
Oh, you know,
a man's gotta eat.
To think that some people
still refuse to believe
in guardian angels.
Booth!
Who's that?
[ Booth ]
Deputy Director Kirby.
My boss's boss's boss.
You're what's known as a real
pain in the ass, Agent Booth.
Yes, sir.
I just had my testicles
handed to me...
by the attorney general of
the United States of America.
He wanted to know why
this Marvin Beckett issue...
wasn't done slowly
and carefully with
greater forethought and tact.
You know what
I told him?
No, sir.
I told him I did not know.
Sir, I had to do it the way
I did it because the F.B.I.--
Not your decision, Booth.
You're suspended without pay.
Gun, I.D.,
security card, please.
Sir, I'm entitled
to the reading
of the charges against me.
The charges against you...
are that I was pissed upon
from a very great height!
You're out of here
in 10 minutes.
Can they do that?
Just kick you out
without any warning?
The two guys standing
behind me with the guns
seemed to think so.
As you can see, Harper's
ribs and sternum were
practically obliterated...
by the two shots
to his torso.
Zack, Booth got fired.
- Suspended, not fired.
- Suspended's F.B.I.-speak
for fired.
Do you know what hurts
the most? They took the car.
I got no wheels.
The bullets themselves
were removed from the body.
- But Hodgins found some
very small fragments.
- Copper, lead, polymer.
I mean, this is
a conspiracy, baby.
Guys, what we're dealing with
here is that Booth won't be
working with us anymore.
Well, I got my own gun.
It's just, God, why did they
have to take the company car?
I assume that the only way
Booth can get his car back...
would be to solve
the case on his own
and that we'd help.
Oh, no. No, no.
I can't let you guys do that.
Anyone who wants to help Booth,
raise their hands.
All right, I reverse engineered
to find the most likely design
of the bullets.
After the bullet spread,
lead pellets were released
like buckshot.
Wait a second.
That's a homemade round
invented back in the '70s.
- We're talking a military-issue
M-40 A-1 sniper rifle.
- Nice.
Dude, what you call being
a conspiracy theorist,
I call being well-informed.
Wait.
Gus Harper was murdered
by a military sniper?
- Who makes his own rounds.
- Maybe we could compare it to
the bullet that grazed Russ.
I'm a civilian.
We don't have access
to that round.
Maybe Caroline can help us.
[ Booth ]
You still have a job?
Not for long.
I'm on performance review.
None of the F.B.I. members
of the Bank Robbery Task Force
had sniper training in the '70s.
I need to know who else
was on that task force.
Local--
Booth! Booth!
I got it figured out.
State cops, A.T.F.
And if any of 'em had sniper
training. Once you find out,
you keep your head down.
As.
Task force, sniper training,
'70s, duck. Got it.
I figured out a way to solve
the case and get your job back.
Wow. That'd be great.
We need my father to give us the
rest of the evidence he stole
from that safety-deposit box.
Great.
I'll drive.
Dr. Saroyan,
when I get my doctorate,
I'd like to work here.
Zack, you are
an excellent scientist.
But an important part
of the job is appearing
as an expert witness in court.
- Ooh.
- "Ooh," what?
Jurors have to take you
seriously. And frankly,
you look like a weekend fill-in
at a college radio station.
Truth hurts, dude.
Learn from it and grow.
[ Chuckles ]
You weren't able to find Max
by tracing him through the
cell phone call he made to me?
Call came over
the Internet.
It was untraceable.
Well, Max always
did things his way.
Guess your being
a priest didn't have much
of an affect on him.
Son, I spent my whole life
trying to turn Max's life
to Jesus.
He knows exactly
one Bible verse.
Numbers 35:19.
"The revenger of blood himself
shall slay the murderer.
When he meeteth him,
he shall slay him."
What's that mean?
That's the law
of the jungle.
Father Coulter, if my father
makes contact with you again,
please tell him
he needs to trust me.
His way got my mother murdered
and almost got Russ killed.
- It's time he tried my way.
- He won't contact me again.
- Well, how do you know?
- Ask him.
He put me under surveillance.
If a parish priest
can figure out the F.B.I.
is watching him,
so can an experienced
fugitive like your father.
I need a makeover.
[ Sighs ]
Zack, I am a big believer
in people being themselves.
You're actually
kind of cute.
Yes. I've been told that
many times.
Usually followed
by the word "but."
In this case, "But no one
takes you seriously."
I need help, Angela.
So, what do I do first?
Lose the floppy hair.
[ Groans ]
Why are you mad at me?
[ Sighs ]
I need a gun.
No, you don't.
You got me. I'm your gun.
You want equipment?
Here. Have these. All right?
New division of labor.
I shoot 'em, you cuff 'em.
Why didn't you tell me
you had Father Coulter
under surveillance?
It is my job to find your dad
and put him in prison.
And you don't think
I'll help.
He's your father.
I really don't think I should
have to ask you to help.
He abandoned me, Booth.
And that's the best thing
you can say about him.
Your father lives
by a certain code.
And part of that code
is defending his family
by whatever means necessary.
You mean killing people
and setting their corpses
on fire?
- "Any means necessary"
sort of covers that.
- You respect him?
I'm just saying in his world,
he's a very honorable man.
That's ridiculous.
There's only one world.
It's this one.
Would that be the one world
where you're mad at me for
trying to catch your father?
Or the other world where you
actually want him caught?
Neither.
You have to pick one.
Either. Both.
Dr. Brennan, Agent Booth,
I thought you'd like to meet
the reason we're all losing
our jobs and getting shot at.
This is
Mr. Marvin Beckett.
- I wanted
to thank you personally.
- You're welcome, Mr. Beckett.
Thirty years ago,
crooked agents put me in jail
for something I did not do.
I did not kill
the young F.B.I. agent.
I did not steal the money.
And I thank you for proving it
to the world.
That's why I'm here to tell you
to your face, to assure you,
I did not do those things.
You freed an innocent man.
And in return,
I must warn you,
the people that did this
to me aren't just a bunch
of corrupt cops.
They serve masters
of much greater influence.
You're looking to bring their
world down around their ears.
They will strike at you.
Of you.
Watch yourselves.
Here's your list of snipers
from the decade of disco.
This time I'm advising you.
Duck.
Anyone you know?
Yeah.
The A.T.F. rep on the task force
was a marine sniper,
Robert Kirby.
F.B.I. Deputy Director
Robert Kirby?
That just suspended you?
Call your brother, tell him
to get out of the house.
Tell him to get out now.
Why? What's going on?
That concept.
Seconds after Caroline
got this list,
Kirby knew about it.
He's not answering.
I don't understand, Booth.
It's not us that Kirby
is afraid of.
It's your father.
The only way to strike at him
is to go through you or Russ.
Kirby was the one that
took a shot at Russ.
No answer.
Russ?
Hello?
- All right, just stay back.
- Russ?
- There's no sign of a break-in.
I'll check the back. Russ?
-  Russ?
Oh, my God.
Booth?
What?
Russ.
Just take it easy, all right?
We don't know that for sure.
That's too much blood.
Nobody could survive that--
that much blood loss.
Nobody.
All right. Okay.
It's all right.
Oh, my God.
♪♪
I'm not leaving
without these diamonds!
Diamonds?
I'm just here for the stains.
With Persil ProClean.
BOOM.
It's more than Clean.
It's Persil ProClean.
Inside your I there's an everyday battle
because life's daily stressors like
smartphones sunlight screens just one
occupied I vitamin a day replenishes
key nutrients that help protect the
health of your eyes take argue via to
take care of your eyes eyes ladies we
all know men don't like to ask for help
weather is asking for directions are
taking care of themselves with your
guys over forty and not feeling like the
man he used to be you may need your
help give him a complimentary sample of
eugenics total T the award winning
number one selling testosterone booster
at gnc just text rich three six nine
three six nine now as men age they had
less and less rita's dost iran in that
can make it harder to stay in shape
eugenics total T is powered by test a
patented key ingredient clinically
validated to beast free and total
testosterone levels they'll be your man
feel leaner stronger with more energy
and drive more path in two new gen X is
available to and retailers that you can
only get his complimentary sample by
texting rich two three six nine three
six nine text now and will include a
battle of new gen X thermo our most
powerful fat incinerator ever that's our
eyes the eight to three six nine three
six nine the results will speak.
What does it fee like
To sell your car to Carvana
It feels amazing, you get a
great offer in seconds
That feels too good to be true
With kicking back and relaxing
As we pick up your car
And when you get paid
on the spot
It feels like scoring big
You know the feeling
You just never imagined
You could get it
from selling your car
Well, with Carvana
You can experience the new way
to sell a car
[school bells]
When pain says, “I'm here,”
I say, “So are they.”
♪♪
ALEVE
- Who do you take it
for?
The whether to last second bake sale.
Taco tuesday or a meal for your future
in laws.
It's going to be great the mccormick by
your side for over one hundred thirty
years it's going to be great.
My life used to be so calm and fun until
one day.
Oh where'd the farm go the cards they
will guide me home you might think you
know how to play solitaire solitaire
grand harbour face challenges to the
next level with exciting ways to play
it'll keep you sharp it's even better
than ordinary so at the end of the day
when you want to wine play solids grand
harvest and explore new world of to
download for free.
Is my friend's death because she's a
reward zadie queen she has the trouble
cash rewards card and I would triple
cash rewards back on pbs and no annual
fee or spend more time focusing on.
Target get top dollar it's sell your
home fast with the very best real
estate agents at ideal agent we
thoroughly research top agents in your
local market we analyze the result we
personally interviewed them and
negotiate a great commission on your
behalf as low as two percent we made
the home sewing spirits simple and easy
while saving thousands in commissions
we saved just shy of nineteen thousand
dollar by using ideally I think the be
able to call ideal agent somebody who's
already bedded the agents and have
somebody that is top notch the whole lot
of work and a whole lot of worry we've
helped thousands of home sellers and
buyers the five-star results bringing
us number one in real estate on
trustpilot there's no obligation or
upfront costs in our services for and
available nationwide call today or
visit ideal agent dot com the best
agents at a great commission guaranteed.
Is the best in her few of those are
victims having I didn't need a couple
of hours because both the best clue to
correct the case that it or you want me
to explain again.
Continues next history.
It's against the law
us not calling in a murder.
In iraq.
It wasn't a murder.
It was a bloodstain.
That much blood,
it's mur-- it's murder.
We call it in, the next thing
is we find ourselves
under arrest.
That had to be Russ's blood.
You got a sample, right?
We'll check the D.N.A.
at the lab.
Until then, who's the one
who always says, "Don't jump
to conclusions"? Right?
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks.
I wish you wouldn't keep letting
me hug you when I get scared.
Hey, when I get scared,
I'll hug you.
We'll call it even.
Results?
The blood's not Russ's.
Even you can't do
a D.N.A. test that fast.
Didn't have to.
Both Brennan and her brother
are "O" type blood,
as was the mother.
The blood sample
you brought me was "AB."
Therefore--
Okay, let's go tell Bones.
I just saw her.
She's on her way
to see the priest.
Why?
He said he had
something for her.
She can't be going places
without me. Not when it's
open season on Brennans.
[ Cell Phone Rings ]
Bones?
[ Caroline ]
Not even close,
chéri.
We need to talk.
Well, first, I want to tell you
that your brother...
is, uh, with his father.
You mean... with God?
No, his earthly father--
your father.
Are you certain?
Saw it with my own eyes.
Oh, thank God.
Which I use only
as a figure of speech.
Well, you have
to start somewhere.
You know, you're--
you're very much like him.
I'm-- I'm nothing
like my father.
Black and white.
The two of you, you always saw
the world in black and white.
Your mother wasn't like that.
Either is Russell.
All right, go.
I was clearing out my desk
when my phone rings.
And it's this F.B.I.
agent named Carlson.
Yeah. He heads up
a surveillance unit.
He tells me you and Booth
are wasting my time
with this damn priest.
I tell him, "You better mind
your mushy mouth."
I gotta find Bones,
keep her from getting killed.
Father Coulter
is 90 years old,
confined to bed with Alzheimer's
in a convalescent home
out there at the seminary.
Which does not much sound like
the priest you told me about.
Your father,
he talked about, uh,
when you were four
and your brother was nine.
And-- And he hid
behind this door and
he jumped out at you.
- You know what? Just give me
the keys to your car.
- My car?
Boo! He hollers, "Boo!"
And you-- you had this doll.
Had this string in the back
for talking.
Chatty Cathy.
Wham!
You took that doll.
And you wound up. And you hit
your brother so hard you knocked
him flat as a pancake.
I said to your mother,
"No one will ever jump out
at that girl again."
And your mother said,
"Just like you, Max.
She's just like you."
Hair color, plastic surgery,
colored contact lenses,
chin and cheek implants,
15 years older.
Still,
I should have seen it.
[ Tires Screech ]
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Line Ringing ]
Come on, Bones.
Pick up. Pick up!
This is Dr. Temperance Brennan.
Leave a message.
Damn it.
Russ knew it was you
all along?
Yeah.
You talk to Russ,
but not to me?
You know,
to tell you the truth,
you do better without me
and Russ does worse.
Take this.
I'm not religious.
No. We're gonna play
this your way. Please.
This is Gus Harper's journal.
There's a key there that's
to a safety-deposit box.
In that safety-deposit box
is all the evidence.
Why didn't you give it
to them back in 1978?
Because your mother took
one look at it and said,
"If you turn this over to them,
they will kill us
and our kids."
They got Mom anyway.
There's not a day that goes by
that my heart is not broken.
[ Vehicle Approaching ]
Dad, come on!
I gotta go.
Wait.
I can't let you go.
Oh, I love you too.
No. I mean,
I can't let you go.
- I'm sorry.
- [ Moans ]
I must be getting old.
I let you get the drop on me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just can't let you get away.
I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
If you find somebody that you
can trust, you hang on to him.
Remember that.
Dad, let's go!
I'm proud of you.
I love you.
Dad, get in.
You take care of her.
- F.B.I. Stop or I'll shoot.
- Booth.
Booth. Booth.
Oh.
Right. Did he really
have to hit the car?
I wasn't gonna chase him.
You okay?
♪♪ [ Indie Rock ]
[ Man ]
♪ And if I only could
♪ I'd make a deal with God
♪ And I'd get him
to swap our places ♪
♪ Be running up that road
♪ Be running up that hill
♪ Be running up that building
♪ If I only could
♪ You don't wanna hurt me
♪ But see how deep
the bullet lies ♪
♪ And if I only could
♪ I'd make a deal with God
♪ And get him to swap
our places ♪
♪ Be running up that road
♪ Be running up that hill
♪ With no problem
♪ If I only could
♪ I'd make a deal with God
♪ And get him to swap
our places ♪
♪ Be running up that road
♪ Be running up that hill
♪ With no problem ♪
What's this?
Zack's doctorate.
I'd like to recommend him
for a job.
I can't put him in front
of a jury. I'm sorry.
I'll put in a good word
in Pure Research. That way, he
can come visit once in a while.
- Visit?
- Dr. Saroyan,
Dr. Brennan, Dr. Hodgins,
I'd like to present
your colleague.
Dr. Zachary
Uriah Addy.
[ Chuckles ]
Look at you.
All grown up.
[ Saroyan ]
Wow.
Very impressive.
I can learn how to be effective
in front of juries.
Zack can learn anything.
All right, he's hired.
Who am I
to break up this team?
Lunch is on me, Dr. Addy.
Anywhere you want to go.
The diner.
Anywhere, I said.
I like the diner.
Hey, do me a favor,
Uriah.
Need a little time
to adjust to
your fascist haircut.
Let's go.
Congratulations,
Dr. Addy.
Thank you, Dr. Brennan.
[ Angela ]
Zack, congratulations.
[ Hodgins ]
Congratulations.
Hear, hear!
[ Hodgins ]
It's about time, man.
Congratulations.
[ Saroyan ]
You should be proud
of yourself.
What happened?
Well, the attorney general took
one look at the, uh, evidence
your father provided.
And, you know,
he reinstated me.
I'm glad.
Listen. We, uh, found
another burned body.
Same place, same setup.
Kirby?
I'm pretty sure.
It was Kirby's blood
in your apartment.
Dad's still trying
to warn people.
Leave me and Russ alone.
Uh, Russ, he's safe
with your father.
They're warning people
to stay away from you.
You know what?
I'm sorry that you had
to go through it again.
Watching your family drive off,
you know, leaving you behind.
I'm sorry.
My father is-- is--
He's your dad.
And he loves you.
Luxury of.
You know, I'm just--
I'm just one of those people who
doesn't get to be in a family.
That's--
Listen, Bones.
Hey, there's more
than one kind of family.
Than one family.
Well, Zack got the job, right?
Come in and
congratulate him.
Nah. These are your squints.
Not my squints.
No. Booth, we are
all of us your squints.
Do me a favor and pat
Zack on the shoulder
with an open hand.
What? Why? Does that
mean something?
[ Chuckles ]