[ Siren Wailing ]
- [ Booth ]
What'd you do?
- I read,
walked on the beach,
chilled--
Oh, you chilled
in Darfur?
- You chilled in Darfur?
- In North Carolina.
I changed my vacation plans
to spend time with my brother.
Russ and I talked about it,
and we really want to find Dad.
Just so you know,
the F.B.I.'s gonna find your
father no matter what you want.
My brother and I
don't want the F.B.I.
to back-burner the search.
- [ Tires Screeching ]
- [ Vehicle Thuds ]
Is it okay to go
on two wheels like that?
Only when making
very sharp turns
at high speeds.
Okay, Bones, why don't
you have a little, uh,
you know, faith in me, okay?
I'm not gonna
back-burner the case, all right?
I'm gonna find your father.
-My brother said you'd say that.
-You really keep saying
"my brother" a lot.
Well, I lost Russ for 15 years.
I like the sound of it.
- My brother.
- [ Siren Continues ]
What's with the siren?
Why are you driving
like a maniac?
[ Siren Stops ]
[ Men Shouting, Chattering ]
A little bit.
[ Booth ]
Two passenger cars
off the tracks, one on the side.
Gonna be fatalities.
Stan, I need some gauze.
Danny, if you don't find..
the owner of this
in the next 10 minutes,
he'll bleed to death starting--
- [ Beeps ]
- now.
- Seeley.
- Camille.
- Don't call me Camille.
- Don't call me Seeley.
Dr. Brennan, Dr. Saroyan.
You two know each other, right?
- No.
- Uh-oh.
-
Dr. Brennan,
I'd like you to check out
the automobile this train hit.
- It's probably
what caused the derailment.
- [ Booth ] Accidental?
N.T.S.B. guy says the train
struck the car at least 200
yards from the nearest access.
- Deliberate?
- Eight minutes, Steve!
Probably suicide.
Why are you still here,
Dr. Brennan?
Because I'm not a coroner,
and I don't work for you.
Well, you got that
half right.
Found him, Cam!
Still breathing!
Thanks, Steve!
All right.
Every survivor's
one less person for me
to autopsy.
[ Exhales ]
You look good
out of your suit, Seeley.
But then you always did.
Yeah, thanks--
It's great to have you back
in D.C., Camille.
One minute
she was holding a severed arm.
The next, she's hitting on you.
No, she wasn't hitting on me.
And you know what?
She is your boss Bones.
No. Goodman's my boss.
May I approach?
- All yours, Dr. Brandon.
- Brennan. Dr. Brennan.
- You want to guess my name?
- No. There are thousands of you
in D.C. and only one of me.
You know what?
While you were away,
Goodman decided...
there should be
a head of Forensics
at the Jeffersonian.
- It never occurred to you
to check in, huh?
- Why didn't Goodman hire me?
- [ Booth ]
My guess? People skills.
- I have people skills.
All right.
That firefighter's name
is Nelson.
This is at least
the fourth time
you've met him.
Odds are Cam knows
his kids' names
after meeting him once.
A lot of jewelry, male.
Thighbone suggests
he was tall.
I.D. bracelet.
It's good-quality gold.
Slightly melted.
Too melted
for a regular car fire.
Do you see a skull?
Hey, Bones.
I'm not looking for a skull.
Burn damage
on the body is more intense
than I'd expect from a car fire,
even if the fuel tank
ruptured and was absolutely full
at the time of impact.
Do you see anything on this car
that isn't ruptured?
- Booth, three deaths
in the first-class car.
- Oh, homicide.
That makes it my case.
- One of them's a senator.
- That makes a difference?
Facts of life, Bones.
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
♪♪
Apparently, Cam
is autopsying a senator.
[ Hodgins ]
A senator? We're movin'
up in the world.
They have a past.
Cam and the senator?
Cam and Booth.
Look how she touches his arm
when he laughs.
You touch my arm
when
I
laugh.
No. No, you touch me.
It's a big difference.
Okay, what do we got?
Male, 40s.
Approximately 6 foot 7.
Right-handed.
Six foot 7?
Athlete in his youth.
Right shoulder is worn
from a repetitive motion.
- Baseball pitcher maybe.
- More like, um--
[ Booth, Zack ]
Basketball.
Six foot 7.
It makes sense.
Every bone in his body
is broken.
Dude, he got hit
by a train.
"W-A-R."
It's all I can make out
of one name.
And then "Love, Brianna."
- Dude!
- You're saying "dude"
way too much.
Forties, 6 foot 7,
W-A-R, Brianna.
This is Warren Lynch.
- [ Brennan, Zack ]
Who's Warren Lynch?
- No way.
Warren Lynch?
Lynchpin International,
- Yeah.
- I am not telling the press...
that Warren Lynch
killed Senator Paula Davis...
before we're completely certain.
[ Brennan ]
I know Senator Davis.
I signed a book for her
to give to her daughter.
Man, I love Paula Davis.
She could've been president.
Warren Lynch and Senator Davis
killed in one accident?
No way it's a coincidence.
Hey, Hodgepodge,
all engines reverse.
First we identify
beyond the shadow of a doubt,
then we get paranoid.
I'm cool.
As long as paranoia's
on the schedule somewhere.
- It wasn't suicide.
- Jagged edges to the breaks,
small fragments,
lack of circular...
or radiating fractures
or adherent spurs.
What does that mean?
This man was dead
for several hours
before the train hit him.
♪♪
♪ [Theme Music] ♪
If you, like many people,
are covered by both Medicare
and your state's Medicaid,
here's something important
to know.
Medicare Annual Enrollment
is here and ends December 7th.
So now's a great time to look
at a UnitedHealthcare Dual
Complete plan.
It could give you even
more health benefits
than you already have.
To find out if you or someone
you care about is eligible,
it's easy...
call now to talk with us.
We can explain it all
and answer your questions.
Medicaid gives you benefits
and Medicare gives you some,
too.
But a Dual Complete plan
can add even more benefits
and features
compared to Original Medicare.
You'll get $0 copays
on all covered prescriptions-
including brand names.
And depending
on where you live,
you could enjoy
other benefits, too.
Like more dental care,
and rides to and from
your doctor or pharmacy.
Most plans even give you up
to $300 a month to help pay
for covered
over-the-counter products,
groceries, and new
this year - utility bills.
And best of all,
with this plan,
there's no extra cost to you.
Remember, if you have
Medicare and Medicaid,
chances are, you could get
a Dual Complete plan.
So call now to talk with us.
Our agents are available
to help.
We know healthcare
can be confusing.
UnitedHealthcare can
straighten things out.
And with over 40 years
of experience...
...you can count on us
to be there for you.
With a Dual Complete plan
you could have $0 copays on
all covered prescriptions...
help paying for covered
over-the counter products,
groceries and utility bills...
more dental coverage, too...
all at no extra cost.
If you have both
Medicare
and Medicaid,
you may be eligible for
Dual Complete.
Hurry, Annual Enrollment
ends December 7th.
So call the number
on your screen now
to see if you're eligible
or to enroll.
There's more for you...
with a UnitedHealthcare
Dual Complete plan.
♪
♪♪
[ Saroyan ]
We are tighter than
a nun's knees on this one.
No press, no conjecture
with anyone outside this room.
Why?
Because we are
gonna find...
the details
of Senator Davis's death...
without giving Oliver Stone
or Michael Moore any ideas.
Are we assuming
Senator Davis's death
was a coincidence?
You wanna kill someone, planting
yourself in front of a train
probably not the best idea.
But too early
to make any assumptions.
[ Sighs ]
I am a diuretic seagull, people.
Everything goes through me.
10:00 a.m., here, tomorro.
"Zackaroni," your turn
to bring the doughnuts.
Zackaroni?
Cam noticed
that I eat macaroni and cheese
every day at lunch.
Every single day?
Yep.
You should be okay
with Dr. Saroyan getting
the head of Forensics job.
Why is that?
Because you are a strictly
rubber to the road,
hardball scientist.
You're not
a flesh-pressing, ink-stained,
policy-making "wank."
You're not
a flesh-pressing, ink-stained,
policy-making "wank."
- What are her qualifications?
- Chief Coroner of New York
for two years.
Assistant Federal Coroner
before that.
- How am I doing?
- Very well. Impressive.
- [ Cell Phone Ringing ]
- Brennan.
We were discussing
her mother's case.
- Fine.
- I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Yes. Good, Dr. Brennan.
We'll chat later.
[ Chuckles ]
It's a very interesting case.
Brennan identified skeletal
remains as her mother's--
killed by a blow to the head.
Initial suspect was her father.
But in the end, we arrested...
a pig farmer-hit man
in Witness Protection.
Added wrinkle,
Brennan gets a call--
Dr. Hodgins?
You're chattering me to death
'cause you hope I'll forget
you called me a "wank".
It's a made-up word.
No meaning.
My name is Lisa Supac, and I am
the Assistant U.S. Attorney
attached to this case.
I'd like to hear first from
the National Transportation
and Safety Board.
Mr. Hobbes?
Thank you.
At 8:04 this evening,
a high-speed commuter train
struck a private vehicle.
The front car derailed,
killing three people,
including Senator Paula Davis.
Preliminary indications
show that the car
was placed there purposely.
Dr. Brennan,
was the Jeffersonian...
able to confirm
that the driver
of the car was Warren Lynch?
Dental records
and physical characteristics
established that.
- Yes.
- The vehicle was registered
to Mr. Lynch.
We'll verify that the jewelry
found on his body was his.
- Plus, we have this.
- [ Beeps ]
[ Supac ]
A photograph
from the carpool lane?
At 1:56 this afternoon,
Mr. Lynch drove illegally
in the diamond lane on I-270.
Our good old
Maryland State Police cameras--
they caught the infraction.
This is definitely
the vehicle found on the tracks.
Nobody saw or heard
from Warren Lynch
after this photo was take.
You can't honestly
expect anyone to believe...
that Warren Lynch
committed suicide
by driving into a train.
Daniel Burrows,
Security and Exchange
Commission.
We were about to lay charges
against Mr. Lynch...
that would not only wipe him out
financially but send him
to prison for several years.
I heard rumors.
But for a man like Lynch
to kill himself--
Mr. Lynch
did not commit suicide.
Dr. Brennan's examination
shows that he was dead
for at least six hours...
before the train
struck his car.
- Dead how?
- I don't know that yet.
But can we assume
that it was foul play?
When it becomes public knowledge
that Warren Lynch is dead,
stock in
Lynchpin International's
gonna plummet.
Well, it sucks for the people
who invested in Lynchpin,
but otherwise--
That's a motive for murder.
How is losing money
a motive?
[ Burrows ]
It's called
shorting the stock.
Basically you bet that
the share price is gonna fall.
And when it does,
you collect.
- How much we talking?
- Tens, maybe hundreds,
of millions.
♪♪
[ Woman ]
Yes, these are
Warren's things.
I bought him the I.D. bracelet
on our first anniversary.
[ Booth ]
"Casu consulto."
- What does that mean?
- Accidentally on purpose.
- Why do you know things
like this?
- It was my husband's motto.
Mr. Lynch wrote about it
in his autobiography.
He played basketball in college.
Made it all the way
to the national championships.
Warren was a high scorer,
but a player on the other team
locked him out of the key.
Warren injured
the opposing player,
sent him to the hospital,
and made it look
completely inadvertent.
"Accidentally on purpose."
He wrote this about himself
as if it were a good thing?
Well, you don't become
Warren Lynch by playing
by the rules.
I'm still his wife.
So this all comes
to me now, correct?
Still his wife,
Mrs. Lynch?
Were you and Mr. Lynch
having marital problems?
Warren and I were separating.
- Why?
- Infidelity.
Hmm. On whose part?
I found out that Warren
was seeing someone.
- Only someone
turned out to be--
- Some dozen.
Hmm.
I'm gonna need a list.
When Brianna confronted Warren,
he had a private investigator
look into her activities.
I admit,
he didn't come up dry.
- Private investigator's name?
- Rick Turco.
He was one of Lynch's
all-purpose, go-to,
dirty-work fixer.
Yeah.
I'm familiar with Rick Turco.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Cheating spouse who stands
to inherit it all.
Corrupt business practices.
And Turco, the private dick.
Where do we start?
Two types of glass
were embedded in
what was left of Lynch.
- We'll start with glass.
- Tempered automotive
safety glass and silicate.
Tempered glass
came from the car windows.
What about the other?
It's 70%
amorphous silicon dioxide.
What's that?
It's a common
domestic container.
Oh. Like a jar.
Why can't we just say a jar?
Anything new, Zackaroni?
Zackaroni?
The victim's left shoulder
and elbow were badly
dislocated postmortem.
You mean between the time
he died and the time
he got hit by the train?
[ Brennan ]
Blood flow was nonexistent
when the dislocation occurred.
Okay.
You guys do this stuff,
and I'll start on Turco.
What's that?
A private investigator.
Turco's an affliction.
I'll set up a meeting
and call you.
You shouldn't
call me Zackaroni.
Yeah. I knew that
the moment I said it.
I'm going to get
a bone mineral density reading.
You didn't actually
want the job, did you?
I don't even know
what the job is.
Well, Goodman will
explain his decision.
Goodman
appointed Dr. Saroyan
while I was on vacation,
then took
a two-month sabbatical
to avoid me.
That explains a lot.
All right.
You know, I think...
it's because
you are very task-oriented.
Zack?
Task-oriented is a euphemism
for lacking overall perspective.
Oh, no. No.
Yeah. Yeah.
A little.
Like, when's my birthday?
I can get the computer
to remind me about birthdays.
[ Sighs ]
That's one of
a gajillion examples.
You could tell me
the other gajillion minus one.
What do you see, Zack?
Uh, bone loss.
Lack of bone density suggests
that Warren Lynch was
much older than his 40s.
But the other
indicators of age--
epiphyseal rings,
cranial sutures--
all disagree.
Age doesn't explain
the ossification of cartilage
where the ribs meet the sternum.
Well, what does explain it?
[ Brennan ] Opiates.
Warren Lynch was
a heroin addict.
♪♪
Agent Booth,
I'm a private investigator.
My greatest asset
is my discretion.
Brianna Lynch already told us
that you work for her husband.
Well, Miss Lynch is welcome
to say whatever she likes.
That client confidentiality
routine no longer exists
when the client is dead.
That's not the assurance
I give my very demanding,
very high profile clients.
That's not the assurance
I give my very demanding,
very high profile clients.
Till death do us not part.
Yeah. How would
your very demanding, very
high profile clients feel...
if they found out
that you procured heroin
for Warren Lynch?
[ Exhales ]
What?
Warren Lynch was
a heroin addict.
I'm gonna open up
a drug investigation on
you, Mr. Turco.
Once the press
gets wind of that, your
very high profile clients...
will find some other
unprincipled Mr. Fix It.
Warren Lynch was a junkie?
- What's your evidence?
- Bones?
Well, so what does
all this mean?
- Sum it up for the man, Bones.
- Warren Lynch suffered
declining bone mass...
due to long-term abuse
of his hypothalamic
pituitary gonadal access.
Nothing says junkie
like your gonads' access, Ricky.
I had no idea.
And I certainly never
procured any heroin for him.
Warren Lynch sure as hell
wasn't trolling for $10 hits
in Lincoln Heights.
Come on, Agent Booth.
You know my rep.
I'm a sin eater.
I make problems go away.
You mean like when Lynch's wife
found out that he was sleeping
with other women?
- Oh.
- [ Sighs ]
All right.
Anything I say,
strictest confidence, correct?
Hmm.
Warren Lynch brought me in
to deal with a blackmailer.
Warren Lynch
was being blackmailed?
By one of his girlfriends?
That would be
my assumption, yes.
I paid 'em off before.
But this was a much bigger deal.
More serious.
- Had to be the heroin, right?
- How'd it play out?
I negotiated the payment down
from a mil to a quarter million,
paid 'em off.
- That was three days ago.
- How?
- Dead drop at Rock Creek Park.
- And you have no idea
who it was?
Well, I had a phone call.
I traced it back.
It dead-ended
on a stolen cell phone.
You did a good job.
Given your heroin bombshell,
I went back
to what tissue remained...
and found traces of
laudanine and reticuline,
alkaloids found
in the opium poppy.
I'd like Angela to do
a facial reconstruction.
Confirm my finding?
It's handy having a pathologist
right in the building.
To turn opium into heroin,
it's exposed to hot
acetic anhydride, which
produces 18 neutral impurities.
The ratio of these impurities
indicates the heroin's origin.
In this case, Mexico.
Mexican heroin is very common.
I-- I wonder if there's
anything we can do
to narrow it down further.
- Gas chromatography--
- [ Beeping ]
shows there was also
fentanyl in the heroin.
What's that?
This reminds me
of when you interviewed me
to be your grad student.
She knows what fentanyl is.
It's a narcotic which boosts
the effects of the heroin.
According to Metro cops,
14 addicts O.D.'d this week
off this one shipment.
Have you told Booth?
I'll leave that to you.
How'd I do?
I thought
she did quite well.
You said you had
something else to show me.
[ Zack ] In a car fire,
gasoline vapor ignites
at 280 degrees Celsius...
and rises to a flame temperature
of 2,200 degrees.
[ Hodgins ]
If the gas tank were full
at the time of impact,
the fire should
have burned for approximately
20 minutes without intervention.
Tell me that's not
a real skeleton.
No. We made him
out of calcium phosphate
and hydroxyapatite.
And Spam.
Twenty minutes now!
That's still a significant
amount of Spam.
And according to
the fire department repor,
the car burned for 40 minutes,
and it still took four minutes
to put out.
- Which means
there was extra fuel.
- And the extra glass you found?
- Five-gallon mason jars.
-
[ Zack ] Six of them.
- Filled with gasoline.
- That or moonshine.
Why does the whole lab
smell like a luau?
Zack and Hodgins are proving
that there was extra accelerant
in Lynch's vehicle.
- Using what medium?
- Artificial bone
covered with Spam.
Turn this off.
- Why wasn't
I told about this?
- [ Chuckles ]
I encourage
independent inquiry.
Your encouragement does not
signify my authorization.
If it happens again,
I will take action.
And I'm from New York,
which means that I will take
New York action. Am I clear?
- Not at all.
- I'm from Michigan.
Dr. Saroyan means
she'll make us watch
musical theater.
Wrong New York.
I'm more from the "get mugged
in broad daylight" tradition.
This is not
a high school science fair.
This is
the Jeffersonian Institute.
Unauthorized experiments
in Forensics will get you fired.
But we're Hodgepodge
and Zackaroni.
- And they work for me.
- What I'd really like to do is
enjoy a meeting of the minds.
But if you insist on
an organizational pyramid,
I will be at the top.
♪♪
[ Booth ]
Spam?
[ Brennan ]
There were mason jars filled
with gasoline in the backseat...
intended to break
when the train hit.
Oh. And they got this
with Spam?
Yeah, Spam.
Hmm. And Cam, she got all
bent out of shape.
She wants to authorize
all experiments.
Great. You know,
Zack and Hodgins,
they do an experiment
with fake bones and Spam.
What is your Spam fixation?
A defense lawyer hears Spam,
he makes a joke,
and the jury laughs.
And everything we get from
the Jeffersonian is framed
as goofy science, you know,
from a bunch of squints
with no connection
to the real world.
That wouldn't happen.
Really?
Like the time
you dropped a dead monkey
down the elevator shaft?
That was to show--
Okay, I take your point.
Cam's goal is
a successful prosecution
in a court of law.
Same as mine and yours.
No. You're all about
finding the truth.
Okay, your words say good,
but your tone says bad.
So it's confusing.
Cam knows
that too much truth...
is just as bad
as too little.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
See? Which is why
she got the job.
Booth.
Angela says that you and Cam
had a sexual relationship. Does
that affect your view of her?
Patch me through.
Wildly out of line.
Just so you know that.
When?
Hmm.
Did you get the doer?
Personal prerogative...
is at the heart
of scientific inquiry.
Bones.
[ Sighs ]
Thanks for the notification.
What?
The man who was charged
with murdering your mother--
The pig farmer,
Vince McVicar.
He was killed.
Today at the Alexandria
Federal Holding Facility.
[ Sighs ]
I don't--
He was the only connection
to my father.
His trial was gonna be my--
How am I ever gonna find out
what really happened?
♪♪
[ Saroyan ]
That's not Warren Lynch.
- How accurate is this thing?
- [ Brennan ] It's not
the machine that's accurate.
It's Angela,
and she's good.
That is not Warren Lynch.
Hey, Zack provided a skull,
and this is the face
that goes with it.
Could it be the wrong skull?
Zack doesn't make
that kind of mistake.
He's also very good.
- What about the dental records?
- I'll check 'em for tampering.
But you're certain
that the body in the car--
Is not Warren Lynch.
Absolutely certain.
All right.
♪♪
- SNHU supported me from
day one to graduation.
The instructors, my advisor,
I think we kind of all
went on a journey together.
- At Southern New
Hampshire University
I don't feel like I'm
burying myself in debt.
It's less than I ever expected
to spend on a college.
- Completing my degree
at SNHU empowered me
when applying for jobs.
They had the exact degree
program I was looking for
to advance my career.
- [Naeem] We had students from
all 50 states, 71 countries.
It's a remarkable group.
- I'm the first of my family
to have a college degree.
So it feels amazing.
- This is where you need
to be, here at SNHU.
- It's the best school
for the world that
we live in right now.
- Whatever's going
on in your life.
Whatever your story
is, you can do it too.
- [Narrator] Next
term starts soon.
Visit snhu.edu.
[ Supac ]
The man in the car
was not Warren Lynch?
No. This was the man
behind the wheel.
You had dental records.
Well, somebody digitized...
Lynch's dental X-rays
and then refilmed them...
utilizing authentic
alphanumeric bar codes.
-The records
were expertly faked.
-Where the hell is Warren Lynch?
I've informed the F.B.I.
that they might want
to start looking for him.
In the meantime,
we're moving to I.D. this guy.
Mistakes like this cannot happen
when the case concerns
a dead senator.
Miss Montenegro uncovered
a fraud. That's the opposite
of a mistake.
Save it for
the press conference,
Dr. Saroyan.
Thank you.
Hey, if you'd made a mistake,
I'd have thrown you
to the wolves.
[ Booth ]
Metro cops hinted the guy
pushing the Mexican heroin...
laced with fentanyl
is Eddie Bean--
young guy,
baldy-headed, 5'5",
145 pounds.
You know,
if drugs were legalized,
they could be dispensed
from clean, safe,
controlled outlets...
by trained personnel--
not in alleyways by criminals.
Yeah, right.
Hey, that's our guy.
Let's go.
Oh, no, no. Shh.
What we gotta do
is we gotta wait until he deals.
Catch him in the act.
We wait?
For how long?
However long it takes.
What do we do while we wait?
This is a stakeout.
We converse.
Well, I tried
to initiate conversation
on the drug war but--
Oh, God, fine.
You know what?
Let's just talk about something
we're not gonna argue about.
[ Sighs ]
Been out
to your mother's grave?
Not since the funeral.
Really?
Why would I?
Well, to connect.
She's dead.
Fine.
You know what?
Forget it.
Dead. As in
gone from this world.
[ Man Shouting, Indistinct ]
Excuse me.
I'm curious.
Um, do you talk
to the headstone?
I mean, what do you--
What do you say?
It looks like
I'm talking to the headstone.
But what I'm really saying
is that--
Forget about
where the words are aimed.
What I say is that...
I remember them.
They can't hear you...
because they're dead.
My mouth moves,
words come out,
but none seem
to get across
the drawbridge...
to the princess I know
who awaits within.
We're on!
What princess?
Hey! Oh, hey, Eddie.
What the hell?
How are you doin', huh?
[ Grunts ]
Pockets.
Watch out for needles.
Don't you have
to read him his rights
before you strangle him?
Empty.
I had to hold
his throat closed...
so he wouldn't
swallow the evidence.
All right.
If you bite me,
I will squeeze
your little pinhead off.
- [ Groaning ]
- [ Gagging ]
Okay. Oh, easy.
- [ Grunts ] There it is!
- You shouldn't swallow heroin.
It's dangerous.
- [ Groaning ]
- Okay. Eddie.
Eddie--
Eddie.
Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
Hey, Eddie.
I'm gonna ask you
a question, okay?
You answer, you walk away.
All right?
You don't answer--
You book me.
I get sick.
I know the drill.
No.
If you don't answer,
I'm gonna cram this
back down your throat
without the protection.
All right, you sold some
of this crap to a tall guy,
over six and a half feet tall.
Show him, Bones.
What?
Show him.
Oh, um--
- Like that tall.
- Uh, nobody I know.
[ Grunts ]
Here. Come on, eat it. Eat.
That's it.
Get it in there. That's it.
[ Coughing, Choking ]
Ray!
Ray?
- Ray! Ray Stewart.
- Tell me about Ray, huh?
Everybody knows him down here.
He's a longtime skel.
When was the last time
you saw him?
He bought a stick of dynamite
about three days ago.
I feel I should alert you.
There's an additive
in this heroin
that causes overdoses.
Well--
Thanks.
- Hey, where'd you find her?
- Museum.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
Oh.
He should warn the addicts.
Yeah. Like they do
on a pack of cigarettes.
When? Thanks.
What?
They found Warren Lynch.
Mr. Lynch was thrown
from a speeding car.
It's a minor miracle
he survived.
It may be because he was already
unconscious at the time.
Unconscious?
Yes.
Badly beaten.
Internal bleeding, broken ribs,
both legs, some spinal damage,
broken pelvis.
When can we talk to him?
Anytime you want,
as long as you don't
expect a response.
This man has
severe brain damage.
Off the record,
he's not going to wake up.
Best-case scenario,
he spends the rest of his life
hooked up to feeding tubes.
This is one of
the richest men
in the country.
Most of the time,
that might mean something.
Not now.
Dr. Lawrence,
this man holds the key...
to how and why
Senator Paula Davis died.
I'm sorry. Anything
that man has in his head,
it's going to stay there.
Excuse me.
♪♪
After Zack nagged me
a hundred times--
It's important for us to explain
how the victim's shoulder
and elbow were dislocated.
[ Angela ]
And I re-created
the most likely sequence.
[ Bones Popping ]
- Ouch!
- The victim was dead
when this happened.
He didn't feel it.
Run it again.
[ Booth ]
That's like he was
putting his jacket on.
Corpses don't usually
do that.
These injuries occurred
when the corpse
was forced into a jacket.
- Yeah. Most likely
by two people.
- Yeah. In a big hurry.
They had a train to meet.
Got anything on
the H.O.V. lane photograph?
Yeah.
It was relatively easy to get
the license plate numbers from
these two cars.
Yeah, well,
I'll check 'em out.
But there was another car.
- In the next lane.
- How do you know that?
- Well, rich guys
keep their cars shiny.
- [ Beeping ]
Adjusting for the diffraction
of light caused by the curve--
It's a Navigator.
But get this.
[ Beeping ]
I don't know if that's
of any use to you.
Yeah. It's of use.
Booth, do either of these
count as experiments?
'Cause if they do,
we could both get fired...
by your old sweetheart.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, you just quit
telling Bones...
who you think
I've slept with.
[ Angela ] Think?
What do you mean, think?
[ Saroyan ] Two people
forced the corpse into a jacket.
That's excellent work.
- Who's that?
- I think it's Rick Turco.
Means Turco's probably
the last person to see Lynch
before he fell off the radar.
Angela and Zack are scared
that this counts
as an experiment...
and you are
gonna fire them.
Ah, I am getting through.
Why did you
take this job, Camille?
- Why shouldn't I, Seeley?
- Because it's basically
herding cats,
and you're a dog person.
- Dogs herd cats.
- Dogs don't do that.
- Chase 'em up trees, whatever.
- Seriously, Cam.
Why did you take this job?
[ Clicks Tongue ]
These are titanium rib clippers
from Germany.
My last job, used bolt cutters
from Home Depot.
These are much, much nicer.
This autopsy table
has downdraft ventilation.
No rotting corpse smell, Seeley.
My last table
didn't even have a drain.
Think about that a second.
Leaky corpse, no drain.
So you took this job
for better equipment.
I've spent my whole
professional life in
basement rooms with no windows.
Now I'm in
the Jeffersonian Institute.
What?
Gotta ask.
You so do not.
Or did you take this job
because of--
[ Laughing ]
Oh, my God. The ego.
[ Mock Chuckling ]
Say it.
Nothing to do with you.
I need Bones
this afternoon.
Okay.
It's about her mother's murder
and her father's disappearance.
Plus, she dedicated
her book to you, so--
It's a legitimate case, Cam.
I know.
I read the file.
- Why hasn't she confronted me?
- About what?
About me being parachuted in
over her head.
- Finds me intimidating, right?
- [ Chuckling ]
Hey, I intimidate people.
Yeah.
Bones doesn't intimidate.
Then what?
You've seen the way
she stares at human remains
before she makes a decision.
Yes.
You're human remains,
and she hasn't made
a decision yet.
How do I help her
make the right decision?
Go for the truth.
Take care of her people.
Oh, and I like the whole
intimidation thing.
I think it's cute.
♪♪
[ Guard Shouts ]
[ Door Buzzes, Slams ]
I got no reason to lie.
I'm facing life at least.
Probably gonna get executed.
What did you do?
Mr. Downs
killed his entire family.
I killed your friend...
'cause he cut
in the cafeteria line and
snagged the last orange juice.
Broke off a sharpened toothbrush
in his jugular.
Mr. Downs,
the man you killed--
McVicar?
He's not my friend.
He killed my mother.
- You come to tell me thanks?
- No.
McVicar was my last chance
to find out some things.
McVicar might've known
something about my father.
I can't ask my father
because he left a message...
on my answering machine
telling me
to stop looking for him.
[ Guard ] Pull 'em out.
[ Guard #2 ]
Full search, both cells.
I'll tell you what.
Maybe...
look at McVicar's murder
as a second message from Max,
one that he didn't use
the phone for.
We never mentioned
my father's name was Max.
- I'm done.
- Did you perform a hit
for Max Keenan?
- You performed a hit
for Max Keenan.
- Take it as a sign from God.
[ Door Buzzes ]
How am I gonna tell Russ
our father ordered the death
of another human being?
If he did that,
and I'm not saying
it happened that way,
then your father took down
the man who murdered his wife.
Good people don't have
other people murdered.
Good people
don't even know how.
Your father buried your mother
in a pair of new shoes
in the cemetery...
with her dolphin belt buckle
that reminded her of you...
because you both
love dolphins.
This does not
make him a good man.
People can be more
than one thing.
We were at a dead end.
Okay? Now we're not.
Okay? We know that your father
got to Mitchell Downs,
persuaded him to kill McVicar.
We find out how he did that,
we're that much closer
to finding out what happened
to your old man.
I mean, that's if
you still want to find him.
I do.
Okay.
Silver lining.
♪♪ [ Soft Rock ]
♪ Once I wanted to be
the greatest ♪
♪ No wind or waterfall
could stall me ♪
♪ And then came the rush
of the flood ♪
♪ Stars at night
turned deep to dust ♪
♪ Melt me down ♪
Warren Lynch was in on it.
Where'd that come from?
He had his own dolphin.
That "N.C., lots of A's,"
national championship ring.
His own dolphin.
All the rest
of his jewelry...
was removed
and placed on the dead man--
his $10,000 watch,
his I.D. band from his wife,
his two other rings.
But not
the championship ring.
That's good, Bones.
The only reason they wouldn't
rip it off his hands is--
Because Lynch was
calling the shots.
And I know exactly
who was in on it.
[ Chuckling ]
So Warren Lynch and I
conspired...
to disappear him
for a few days...
so that we could profit from
shorting Lynchpin stock, huh?
- Well, you know,
that's my thinking.
- [ Laughing ]
[ Turco On Speaker ]
Then dressed a junkie
in Warren's clothes,
planted him in front
of a train and--
Wait.
Did I murder the junkie?
No. Bones said
you probably found him dead.
But what I think
is that you and Lynch...
intended a white-collar crime,
but a senator died.
[ Turco On Speaker, Laughing ]
Then I got all hinky...
and tossed Warren
out of the car at
80 miles an hour.
[ Chuckling ]
Is that a confession?
Nah. Nah.
Just gettin' it straight.
You know, as a professionl
investigator myself,
I have to point out
that blackmailers make
much better suspects.
Well, Lynchpin has no record of
a quarter-million-dollar payout
three days ago.
Well, there's not exactly
a column for blackmail payouts
in the corporate books.
If I'd only agreed
to the full payout,
Lynch might've never been
taken by those animals.
Hey, let's play
a little show-and-tell, huh?
'Cause we can put you
with Lynch moments before
he fell off the radar.
That's maybe me before
We worked together.
[ Chuckles ]
You got nothin'.
Booth.
Do that lying thing.
Could you be more specific?
We tell him Lynch woke up
and gave a statement
incriminating him.
Turco knows the lying thing.
Tell him Lynch said something
only Lynch could say.
Oh, great idea, except for
the "only Lynch could say" part.
[ Gulps ] The ring?
Ah, he'll ask for specifics
of the conversations.
I gotta cut him loose.
What-- He's gonna
get away with it?
Well, you know,
that happens sometimes, Bones.
That's that brown
little smelly part of the job.
Shoulder and elbow.
The junkie's
shoulder and elbow...
were dislocated when they
forced him into Lynch's jacket.
We don't know
if Lynch was there for that.
It took two people.
It was him.
Come on, Booth.
The part of you with
the big gambling problem
must love this idea.
Right there. Mm-hmm.
That's the reason
you didn't get Cam's job.
Oh, two against one.
That's unfair.
- Warren Lynch woke up.
- Ah, and he's talking, right?
Huh? Is he pointing
his finger straight at me?
That's correct.
What's he saying?
He let you take
all of his jewelry except
his championship ring.
No. I asked,
what did he say, in words.
Hey, unless I'm under arrest,
I'm leaving, folks.
Mr. Lynch said it was
difficult getting his jacket
onto the corpse.
Rigor mortis.
You have a train to meet.
You're in a hurry.
And the sound
of the shoulder popping.
[ Bones Popping ]
Then the elbow,
like knuckles popping--
[ Popping ]
only louder.
Sickening.
♪♪
Turco will admit
to helping Warren Lynch
place a dead body...
in Mr. Lynch's car
and rigging it to burn...
with the intent
of moving the market.
Everything else,
including placing it
on the tracks,
he says Lynch did
on his own.
He's lying.
There's a small matter
of proving that in court.
- What's the maximum sentence
on those charges?
- Ten years.
He killed three people.
- And put one in a coma.
- But Lynch deserves to be in
a coma, so it doesn't count.
Look. Turco puts
all the blame on Lynch.
He does 10 years,
and he gets all the money
from shorting the stock.
It's 10 years or nothing.
I can only work
with what I'm given,
and the forensic work
on this was not good enough.
- What?
- You were fooled
by fake dental records,
you baked some Spam.
[ Saroyan ]
What did you want us to do?
- Your jobs.
- Hey!
You want us to do your job.
My people gave you all
the evidence you need...
to fry Turco
with any reasonable jury.
- Forensically--
- We gave you everything
you needed to arrest Turco.
- Arrest is not a conviction.
- We gave you enough to
reject his plea bargain...
and indict him in
the wrongful death
of a senator.
-Indictment is not a conviction.
-You accept that plea bargain,
the investigation stops.
Indict him.
Give us time to give you
what you need.
If you accept this plea bargain,
you don't deserve to be
a federal prosecuto
- Dr. Saroyan--
- Yeah, it's scary.
The whole country will be
watching. You don't want to go
in with less than a sure thing.
But you put my people on
the stand as expert witnesses,
and that's a sure thing.
- [ Together ] Not Zack.
- [ Saroyan ] You tell
the story of what happened...
using the evidence
these people provided.
If you have any ability
as a prosecutor,
you'll win the case.
- Are you finished?
- No, Miss Supac.
In the future, when you have
problems with my team,
you register them with me
in private, not by grandstanding
in a public forum.
♪♪
Okay, um,
I sort of see
why she got the job.
[ Booth ]
Well, looks like
your brother was here.
I never understood the idea
of bringing flowers.
Just for once, Bones,
do what people do.
Okay?
See how it feels.
Come on.
That's it.
I'm gonna go stand over here
while you, uh, you know,
talk to your mom.
I told you,
I don't do... that.
Mmm.
Mom, it's me, Temperance.
[ Scoffs ]
I have questions,
but you can't answer them.
No offense,
but I don't think...
there's anything
here of you but your bones so--
[ Scoffs, Chuckles ]
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
Was Dad a good man or...
a bad man?
He had someone killed.
Had him murdered and--
[ Whimpers ]
What's the truth?
Do I--
Do I keep looking,
or do I let it go
like he asked?
Who's he protecting,
himself?
Or me and... Russ?
[ Exhales, Sighs ]
Booth,
I asked the questions,
and guess what.
- No answer.
- Well, maybe
if you weren't standing...
right on top of her,
took a step to the left,
showed a little respect.
Sometimes it takes a while
to get an answer, okay?
Just leave the flowers.
I get answers at a lab.
You get them from people.
Nobody gets answers
from a slab of stone.
Yeah? I see an answer in the
stone. You buried your mother
as Christine Brennan,
the woman that you knew
as your mother,
and not by her real name,
Ruth Keenan.
That tells me who you are.
- What do you got?
- A dolphin.
♪♪ [ Soft Rock ]
What does that tell you?
My father was here.
Because he loves your mother...
and grieves her loss,
and he came here
to talk to her.
You're tainting evidence.
It's not that kind
of evidence, Bones.
It's evidence
of something else,
something that can't be tainted.
♪♪ [ Continues ]
It's beautiful.
Yeah.