[man on TV]
...about tomorrow.
If you do, say so.
(woman)
Not towel right now.
(man)
What?
Why?
You wanna throw in
the towel?
(woman)
No, I don’t wanna throw in
the [bleep] towel.
I thought that’s
what you said.
I’m not upset
about anything.
[door opens]
(woman)
Where the [bleep]
are we going?
What are you doing
down here?
I thought you usually had lunch
with Coma Guy.
This is Vegetative State Guy.
Better company.
Hey, hey, tell him about
those Sherpas
you dropped acid with
in St. Patrick’s Cathedral.
You stole my prescription pad,
And euphoric.
and you forged my name.
What did you tell the cop?
I lied.
They’d have put you away
for ten years.
After they took your license
to practice medicine.
So everything’s good, then.
I  lie to the cops.
There is no case
unless they can prove
that either I got
the drugs illegally
or I sold them
illegally.
I didn’t do the second.
You lied about the first.
Game over.
Yeah.
Tritter’s just playing.
He’s gonna see
how clever you are,
and then just walk away.
The important thing is
that you keep prescribing
the same amount
of drugs to me,
or it’ll look suspicious.
Here’s another way
to look at it.
Having forced me
to lie to the police,
your first concern
is securing
your drug connection.
[door opens]
Joining my father for lunch?
I should’ve called ahead
for a table.
Dr. House was just--
Enjoying a Reuben.
It’s okay.
After ten years,
anything that’ll get doctors
in the same room as--
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Chips?
Wanna see something
really cool?
Some people really cool.
I saw you leaving
last Tuesday.
Practically tripped
over two guys on your way out,
but you had no problem
opening doors.
It’s called akinetopsia.
You can’t see things
when they move.
And since you haven’t
been hit by a bus,
I assume that
it’s intermittent.
It’s probably accompanied
by seizures,
which made me think
that I could set one off
by flashing the--
[grunting]
Gotta love this family.
♪
I can see fine now.
I’ve had seizures before.
Most of the time,
they’re small.
Doctors ran me
through all the tests.
Couldn’t find anything.
Any history of epilepsy
in your family?
The only things I know
that run in my family
are a lot of chutzpah
and the ability to sleep
for ten years.
Although I’m not
really an expert.
Dad never really liked
my mother’s side
of the family,
and after she died
and he came here,
I was raised
by a guardian.
I wouldn’t even know how
to get in touch with him.
How ’bout your father’s side
of the family?
Any relatives
we could speak with?
My father was an only child.
And my grandparents are dead.
Well, who did you put down
as the person the hospital
should contact
in an emergency?
I left it blank.
(Cameron)
There’s gotta be someone.
A friend?
Oh, plenty of friends.
Just...no one that would care
if I was here.
Say, do you mind passing me
my backpack?
[glass clinks]
[Kyle laughs quietly]
Hair of the dog.
(Cameron)
Could be infection.
(Foreman)
Or a brain tumor.
Says he had a CT.
What’s wrong with the simplest
explanation?
Trauma.
He didn’t report
any injuries.
being an alcoholic,
either.
Drinking equals
falling down,
equals trauma, equals--
Maybe it’s inherited.
How would you jump to genetics
from his EEG?
Gene.
All you’ve got are some
vaguely epileptiform waves.
It’s not his EEG.
It’s his father’s.
When it comes
to cortical seizures,
like father, like son.
Small seizures
aren’t unheard of
in a patient
in a vegetative state.
Similarities are
interesting, though.
What caused
the vegetative state?
His house burned down.
Went back in
to get his wife.
Firefighters found him
unconscious three feet
from the bedroom,
asphyxiated.
Not an inherited condition.
Test his DNA.
Start with
adrenomyeloneuropathy.
Check out the home.
[pensive music]
♪
He has a single bed.
[laughing]
They still make single beds?
Could mean he just
doesn’t have sex--
though there were condoms
in the apartment.
House asked you to check out
the home for toxins.
No mold, no leaks, no pets.
(Cameron)
MRI and LP are both
inconclusive.
Infection’s still possible.
Tumor’s less likely, but--
DNA?
Adrenomyeloneuropathy test
was negative.
DNA test again.
Try Unverricht-Lundborg
and late-onset Lafora’s.
(Chase)
Genetic tests take forever.
You can’t just keep testing
for every inherited condition
you think it might be.
Well, not me.
I’ll be leaving early.
But you guys can.
You said no one’s been sick,
but what about delivery people,
repair guy?
I wouldn’t know.
I work from home.
Haven’t been to the office
in over a month.
(Cameron)
Visitors?
Haven’t had any.
The only person I’ve seen
in the last week
was the pizza delivery guy.
And he looked
pretty healthy.
There’s gotta be someone
you’re close to.
[sighs]
Actually, the person
I see most often
is my father.
He’s asleep,
so he can’t stop me.
[groans]
What is it?
Just feeling
a little nauseous.
Oh, my--
I think his liver’s failing.
Oh, God, does--
does that mean that I’m...
[dramatic music]
♪
(Foreman)
Need a central line kit.
Two units of packed
red blood cells,
Field.
type O negative.
He’s unconscious
and heading for a coma.
He’s at a four
on the RLAS scale.
[sighs]
Stop all treatment.
You think this is a reaction
to our meds?
Well, they’re obviously
not helping.
Given the fact
that he’s an alcoholic,
there’s a good chance
his liver wasn’t so hot
when he came in.
Anti-seizure drugs could have
just pushed him over the edge.
We take him off those meds,
what do we put him on?
I was hoping you’d know.
May be academic,
but I just started him
on dialysis.
Kidney and liver failure.
Not too many people
come back from that.
(Cameron)
Trauma’s out of the picture.
It could still be infection.
Or neurological.
Or genetic.
We need
a better history.
(Chase)
Did you miss the part
where the patient
lost consciousness?
L-dopa?
You’re not waking Kyle.
You’re waking his father.
I commend your
observational skills.
You have no reason to think
any amount of drugs
will wake a man
from a coma.
Vegetative state.
Much easier.
This guy’s no Terry Schiavo.
His brain’s all there.
He moves around.
His muscles
have barely atrophied.
Just waiting
for a fairytale kiss.
After I do that,
I’ll stick a needle in him.
The amount
of amphetamines alone
would be dangerous,
besides whatever the hell else
you’ve got in there.
There are reports
out of South Africa
about a pill
that’d temporarily revive
someone in a vegetative state.
We’ve all seen Awakenings.
Made me cry.
I wanna cry.
(Cuddy)
Put the syringe down.
[Mexican accent]
I can out-draw you,
mysterious stranger.
We don’t experiment
on helpless patients.
Be reasonable.
There’s no way this
is gonna work.
Even if you woke him,
it would only be
for a few hours.
A day, two at the most.
You’re risking his life.
I’m risking getting sued.
That’s the only
objection here.
You’ll be torturing him.
And his family.
Good news for legal.
The only family he’s got
is upstairs dying.
Hey!
[tense music]
♪
I want this patient
monitored
for the next 24 hours.
I want someone
with him at all times
to make sure
you didn’t kill him.
I want your ass
in my office!
[groans]
(Gabe)
God.
I’m starving.
[grunts]
I could really go
for a steak.
(Cuddy)
Do you know your name?
You know where you are?
Gabriel Wozniak.
I don’t know the name
of this hospital.
How much are three and five?
Eight.
Also known as half of 16,
a quarter of 32,
two to the third power.
Coolest thing ever.
Any history of seizure
in your family?
No.
Liver disease?
How long have I been here?
I--
I got the feeling it’s, um,
been a long time.
(House)
Interesting.
If your internal clock
kept ticking,
how deep does that
awareness go?
Pick up scraps
of conversations?
You have the vague sense
that the hospital administrator
dresses like a trollop?
Or that the new
Star Wars movies
were a disappointment?
[scoffs]
I know my wife is dead.
I don’t know how long
it’s been.
Ten years.
What’s the last thing
you remember?
The fire.
My wife was in the bedroom.
She had taken
a sleeping pill.
I got...Kyle out.
Went back in for her.
I knew I didn’t make it.
I’m sorry.
What about your wife’s side
of the family?
Any history
of seizures there?
Your son Kyle
is a patient here.
I’m afraid his condition
is serious.
He may be dying.
No seizure issues
on my wife’s side, either.
What about that steak?
Nobody ever answered me.
[elevator bell dings]
Ah.
Rumor in the cafeteria was
Caustic Guy was waking up
Coma Guy.
Technically,
Vegetative State Guy
was woken by...
yeah, Caustic Guy.
So what happened?
Gotta get him a steak
before I can ask him
any more questions.
He doesn’t want to talk
about his son?
Didn’t seem
to emotionally register
that his son is sick.
Brain issue?
He was asphyxiated,
spent ten years
as asparagus.
Who knows what damage
is in there?
It’s possible.
Of course, there’s always
the simple explanation.
Maybe he just
doesn’t like his son.
Only in your world
would that be simple.
The delusion that
fathering a child
installs a permanent geyser
of unconditional love--
Maybe your father’s feelings
were conditional.
Not everyone’s--
Yes, well, of course,
that would play into your
romantic vision of--
In terms you would understand,
we have an evolutionary
incentive
to sacrifice
for our offspring.
Our tribe,
our friends.
Keep them safe.
Except for all the people
who don’t.
Everything is conditional.
Just can’t always anticipate
the conditions.
[pensive music]
♪
Mind if we talk
for a few minutes?
How many pills
would you say
Dr. House takes a day?
I’m uncomfortable
setting a number.
Mm, try.
Six.
A day.
Has he ever had you...
write prescriptions
for him?
No.
What is it
you want me to say?
That he takes too many pills
and is a danger to the hospital?
Or he takes too few
because he’s selling them
on the side?
Either one is ridiculous.
I meant the former.
You’re wrong.
Can I ask what
Dr. House has done
to deserve your loyalty?
He’s not known
as a great boss.
He’s not even much
of a friend.
I mean, look how he left
Dr. Wilson holding the bag.
It’s odd.
You don’t know about that.
You defend him,
and he won’t even tell you
what’s happening
in his life.
[pager beeps]
Me.
[hurried footsteps]
I was paged.
We saw you with the cop.
What’d he want?
How many pills
does House take,
did I ever write him
a prescription,
that sort of stuff.
I told him six.
A day,
or in a mouthful?
I was just hoping you guys
would stay consistent with--
He wants to talk
to us, too?
You’re next.
We’ve gotta tell House
what’s going on.
Tritter says no.
Then no it is.
Cops have a thousand ways
to make life difficult for you.
[door slides open]
Quick, what’s
the kid’s status?
I gotta get back
to our sleeper
before he goes looking
for the orgasmatron.
See, if that were rhetorical,
it would mean that I could
just turn around and leave now.
Which I’m not doing.
From which you should deduce--
He’s off all drugs
except the antibiotics.
His liver’s just managing
to hang in there.
He’s still sliding
into coma.
Your barber sucks.
Hey.
Coma diet.
I could make
a fortune.
Vegetative state diet.
Hmm.
Who gave you your clothes?
Dr. Cuddy.
I guess I’ll need
all new ones anyway.
Everything went
in the fire.
Ah, don’t worry about it.
We use recyclable clothes now.
Wear them once,
then eat them.
Your son’s
measles vaccination.
Do you remember if he had it
and what type it was?
Man, you’re a piece of work,
you know that?
[sighs]
You weren’t gonna tell me,
were you?
I don’t need new clothes.
Dr. Cuddy says my body
will adjust to the drugs.
That I’ll be a vegetable again
by tomorrow.
If I’m really lucky,
the day after.
Yeah.
If I got a day to live,
I’m not gonna spend it
in the hospital room
being grilled.
(House)
Come on, where you gonna go?
Your house burned down.
Your wife’s dead.
The business was sold off.
The only thing
you have left
is down the hall
heading for a liver biopsy.
Used to be this little, um,
hole in the wall.
Run by a guy
named Giancarlo.
Made the best hoagies
in the world.
Real Italian rolls.
Prosciutto.
Provolone.
[clicks tongue]
Mmm.
How far is Atlantic City
from here?
You have one day to live.
And you want a sandwich?
People on Death Row
get a last meal.
State provides it.
Who’s providing for you?
You got a car?
Money?
You’re negotiating with me.
[ATM whirs]
Take out another hundred for me.
And I need your car.
I’m not doing you
any favors.
You’ll get it back tomorrow.
Two days, max.
Road trip.
This is like trying
to control the weather,
but I’d prefer it
if you didn’t eat in the car.
I just had it detailed.
I drive.
Oh, the hell he does!
Sure.
Aside from the fact
he just woke up
from a vegetative state,
the guy doesn’t have
a license.
How ’bout this?
Cops stop us, we lie.
You know how to do that.
Chips!
It’s all the drugs
pumping through his system.
Right now, his reflexes
are better
than Dale Earnhardt Jr.’s.
Hey, what’s this?
It says, "Ip-od."
I’m coming.
[tires squeal]
(House)
So let’s talk
about toxic exposure.
(Gabe)
What was wrong
with the old colors?
I trusted brown.
Do the purple ones
have chocolate inside?
Raspberry cocaine.
This house that burned down.
Where was it?
Moorestown, New Jersey.
Listen, I really need
to know about the candy
because I’m allergic
to berries.
You didn’t mention that.
Is it significant?
No.
So where else did you live?
List everywhere,
including vacations.
Start with when your wife
got pregnant.
We lived in Jersey.
Then we moved to Jersey.
From there, Jersey.
What are you waiting
to hear?
About the little cottage
in the Amazon
with the mosquitoes
and the lead paint
all over the walls?
Yes.
You know what?
I didn’t let you
come along
so you could suck all the fun
out of my one day of life.
Well, you’re outta luck,
’cause that’s totally
why I’m here.
Okay.
Rule change.
Nah.
Person with the money
makes the rules.
Or in this case,
the person who’s friends
with the person with the money
makes the rules.
Well, you want answers
more than I want money.
All right,
so here’s the game.
Ask whatever you want.
But for every question
I answer,
you have to answer one first.
And why would you care
about anything
I have to say?
The day before I died,
I was a successful man.
I had a factory
with over 200 employees.
People listened
when I talked.
I liked power.
Now the only power
I have left
is the power to annoy you.
Took Wilson’s assistant
for coffee.
Why?
Something Tritter said.
She told me the police think
that House stole
Wilson’s prescription pad
and forged his name.
You...believe it?
Do you?
Oh, absolutely.
I do.
I’m just checking
how naive you are.
He’s not gonna steal
his best friend’s pad,
jeopardize his career.
Until his best friend
says no to him.
(Foreman)
House is a junkie.
Junkies do whatever
they have to do
to get what they need.
Kyle’s down to a three
on the RLAS scale.
He’s only showing
localized response.
[sighs]
I’ll call House.
Tell him we’re gonna need
an answer soon.
(Wilson)
Get in your right lane
for 295.
And pass me
the Twizzlers.
I’m curious.
No, you’re not.
Why would a man’s
first instinct be
to drive away
from the only family he’s got?
No!
This is no time for you
to do your thing.
We don’t care
about his state of mind.
if he’s happy.
This factory of yours.
What did you make?
[sighs]
So ask me a question.
I’m thinking.
Only six left,
by the way.
So sign my name.
You don’t need a doctor.
You need a pen.
What is up
with you two?
Wilson lied to the bulls
to keep me out of the big house.
Are you out of your mind?
Well, who’s he gonna tell?
By tomorrow night,
he’s gonna be
a mindless stalk of celery.
Since I answered that one,
by the way,
my turn.
What did you make
in your factory?
Luxury boats.
Have you ever been in love?
Wow.
Going right for the closets
with the embarrassing stuff.
Good move.
Yes.
Describe the boats.
35- to 65-foot hulls.
Twin engines,
parquet floors in the galleys,
staterooms with queen beds.
How’d you meet?
She shot me.
These boats.
I assume you used
mildew-resistant paint
on the hulls?
Naturally.
Shot you?
Paintball.
Doctors versus lawyers.
You ever take your son
to the factory?
Sure.
He used to run
all over the place,
but it was perfectly safe.
Ever love anybody else?
No more questions.
I got my answer.
While Dad’s in the office,
son’s watching them
spray-paint.
And what kid wears a mask?
Mercury specifically targets
the central nervous system.
Are you saying
this was my fault?
Mercury poisoning explains
the seizures.
The liver is like
a big soup strainer.
Soup runs through.
Chicken dumplings stay.
For soup, read blood.
For chicken dumplings--
I get it, I get it.
Mercury.
Sits more or less idle
until your kid
pours tequila shooters
into his liver.
When the liver goes,
takes out the kidneys.
Explains everything.
Yeah, it’s me.
[House on phone]
Foreman, draw blood.
Test for mercury poisoning.
Chase.
Start heavy metal chelation
while we’re waiting
for results.
Chase isn’t here.
I’ll start the--
Where is he?
The lab.
How many pills
does he take a day?
It’s hard to say.
Pain levels vary over time.
Could be six, eight, ten.
Mm-hmm.
Ever write any prescriptions
for him?
Yes.
Why?
Did he tell you to?
He asked me to.
Hmm.
Medicine...
attracts people who are
attracted to power.
I know how he hates
when he is defied
by a patient.
I doubt he handles defiance
from his staff any better.
Now, you correct me
if I’m wrong.
But I don’t think Dr. House
asks for anything.
I think he takes it.
And I think
that you are stuck
lying to the police
to cover up something...
you didn’t want to do.
[pensive music]
♪
(House)
We have been up and down
St. James
like a Monopoly car.
It’s not here.
Giancarlo has left the
building.
We can still turn around
and go back to Princeton.
No!
We’ve come this far.
I’m getting the hoagie.
If your son does have
mercury poisoning,
there’s a good chance
he’ll respond to the chelation.
You might be able
to have a few minutes with him
before you lapse.
Why are you so concerned
about me?
Deep inside, Wilson believes
that if he cares enough,
he’ll never have to die.
Your behavior isn’t normal.
[scoffs]
And you would know normal.
What could he have done
that you won’t forgive
after ten years,
when this is your last chance?
My son is what he is.
His mother’s side?
All drunken losers.
He’s gone the same way.
House told you that drinking
had damaged your son’s liver.
I just said that.
But you didn’t hear him
say that
till after we left
the hospital.
So why did you leave?
(House)
Maybe your son
takes after your side.
Seizures and an allergy
to emotional connections.
Okay, okay, okay.
Enough.
We’re in Atlantic City,
and my time’s not up yet.
We’ll find a hotel
with a casino.
[monitor beeps]
BP’s starting to drop.
O2-sat’s down to 70.
[tense music]
0.3 milligrams of epi in.
Of.
What are you trying to do?
Make him bleed faster?
Check the pulse.
It’s not his liver.
[beeping]
It’s the heart.
(Wilson)
I understand
he’s a French chef,
but I’m sure
he can handle this.
We need a 12-inch
Italian roll,
oregano vinegar--
No.
Not balsamic vinegar.
Oregano vinegar.
Quid pro quo, Clarice.
Game’s still on.
I thought the answer
was mercury poisoning.
What other questions
would you care about?
If you each
had one day to live,
you’d look
for one last meal,
and House would look
for one last answer.
No, can you just send
the ingredients up here?
And I’ll make it myself.
Last ten years.
How much awareness
did you have?
I don’t know.
I knew it wasn’t
the next day.
I--I knew that--
I recognized your voice.
How often were you
in my room?
No.
You’re wasting a question.
I have a better one.
Why steal my pad?
(House)
Oh, my God.
You’re right.
I’m an addict.
Thanks for opening my eyes.
No, I mean, why my pad?
Foreman, Cameron,
and Chase’s pads
are just as convenient.
But their association
with you is involuntary.
They’re employees.
I associate with you
through choice.
And any relationship
that involves choice
you have to see
how far you can push
before it breaks.
This is easy.
You ask the questions,
answer them,
and make tasty snacks.
Let’s go try the casino.
And one day,
our friendship will break.
And that’ll just prove
your theory
that relationships
are conditional,
and you don’t need
human connection,
or deserve it,
or whatever goes on
in that rat maze
of your brain.
Sorry. If I’d known
he was gonna be
this annoying,
I would’ve stolen
Dr. Cameron’s pad
and Dr. Foreman’s car.
[cell phone rings]
At least she appreciates
my brooding melancholy.
House’s House of Whining.
State your complaint.
Patient’s BP just dropped
like a stone.
Do an echo.
Mercury isn’t likely
to damage--
It didn’t.
Mercury test was negative.
Do an echo.
I was wrong.
Your son’s still dying.
I need to go over
every relative
you ever had again.
This time,
forget their diseases.
Just tell me
how they died.
We don’t have time
to take turns.
Gimme the answers.
You get a big one at the end.
You can go for
whatever you want.
Destroy my privacy,
my dignity.
Gay nor dot com now.
Your grandmother?
Heat exhaustion.
Fourth of July picnic.
The woman was 92.
Does anyone in the kitchen
know the hoagie shop
that used to be
on St. James Place?
Your sister-in-law
with the diabetes.
As far as you know,
is she still alive?
She’s not.
Killed in a traffic accident
driving home
from a Phillies game.
I’m sure a lot of beer
was consumed.
Phillies lost.
Your father?
Old age.
Heart finally gave out.
Your wife’s father?
Hit-and-run.
Walking the incontinent dog.
Uh, hi.
Do you guys deliver?
Let me put it this way.
If you deliver,
there’ll be a $100 tip
in it for you.
Excellent!
Victory.
Ha, ha, the night
is finally going my way.
Wilson, toss me a soda.
[dramatic music]
♪
Shall we go somewhere
to talk?
House is an ass.
But he obviously needs
pain medication.
How much pain one person feels
is not a call
the government
should be making.
So you think I’m a bureaucrat
with a badge
following some
arbitrary guideline.
Yeah...I do.
Oh.
So you’re saying I should...
just trust him.
Do you?
You’re not qualified
to make that--
I’m not sure you are,
either.
I’ve been a cop
for 20 years,
and not a day goes by
that someone doesn’t try
to sell me some
self-serving story.
If you had my job,
you’d know.
Everybody lies.
Think you’ve run out
of relatives.
So...
It’s my turn.
Why did you become a doctor?
That’s the big question?
I gave you complete license
to humiliate me,
and that’s the best
you can do?
Well, okay.
Let’s discuss the wonder
of the human body.
No, no, no.
You’re a curious guy.
You like to figure things out.
Why not go into research?
Why work with people
when you...
obviously hate people?
Oedipal fixation.
I was seeking
my mother’s love,
and she thought that Ben Casey
was just the dreamiest--
Okay, fine.
You don’t think you’ll need
any more answers from me?
Give me a hard time.
When I was 14,
my father was stationed
in Japan.
I went rock climbing
with this kid from school
and he fell, he got injured,
and I had to bring him
to the hospital.
We came in
through the wrong entrance
and passed this guy
in the hall.
It was a janitor.
My friend came down
with an infection
and the doctors
didn’t know what to do.
So they brought in...
the janitor.
He was a doctor.
And a Buraku.
One of Japan’s untouchables.
His ancestors had been
slaughterers,
gravediggers.
And this guy,
he knew that he wasn’t
accepted by the staff.
Didn’t even try.
He didn’t dress well.
He didn’t pretend
to be one of them.
The people that ran
that place,
they didn’t think that he
had anything they wanted.
Except when they needed him.
Because he was right.
Which meant
that nothing else mattered.
And they had
to listen to him.
[monitor beeping]
Thank you.
[beeping speeds up]
[grunting]
Need 20 milligrams
of diazepam in a syringe.
[Kyle grunting]
[sighs]
(Cameron)
Heartbeat’s irregular
and accelerating.
(Cameron)
It’s at 200.
He’s gonna crash.
Allergic reaction
to the diazepam?
Better hope so.
It’s either that,
or his heart’s done.
Oof!
What happened on the night
of the fire?
Yeah, I’m sure it’s a stressful
emotional question.
Suck it up.
My wife had taken
a sleeping pill
and gone to bed.
It was Christmas Eve.
I let Kyle pop corn
in the fireplace.
He managed to...
knock loose some tinder.
Wrapping paper
caught on fire.
It spread.
So fast.
I got Kyle out.
And when I went
back in for...
You’re a disappointment.
You act as though
you don’t need anybody.
You--
You just blame your son
for what happened.
I don’t blame him.
He was a 12-year-old boy.
You don’t blame a kid
for an accident.
Then what are we doing here?
Why aren’t you with him?
Because it wouldn’t matter!
I failed to keep
my family safe!
I couldn’t stop the fire.
I couldn’t save my wife!
Now you want me
to stick around watching
while I fail
to save my son?
Thank you so much
for waking me up!
How did your son
dislodge the tinder?
[scoffs]
God.
He dropped the popcorn tray.
He had been complaining
it was too heavy.
I should’ve listened.
And the hit-and-run.
Walking the pissy dog.
That happen at night?
I think so, yeah.
Why?
Car accident
after the Phillies lost.
Night game?
[sighs]
Ragged red fiber.
It’s an inherited condition.
Dropping things,
muscle weakness.
Poor night vision.
Makes people seem
uncoordinated,
accident-prone,
careless.
It’s transmitted
in mitochondrial DNA.
So it only passes
through the mother.
Your wife’s family
weren’t drunks.
They were sick.
It wouldn’t have affected
his liver.
The kid is a drunk.
He thinks that he killed
his mother
and turned his father
into a vegetable.
I might have
a few shots myself.
Foreman.
Test his DNA
for ragged red fiber.
It’s not gonna--
Here’s a thought.
Why don’t we not assume
that the test is negative
until we actually do it?
House.
The kid has severe
cardiomyopathy.
Alcoholic.
No shot at a transplant.
So yeah, maybe you
figured out why.
Good for you.
But he’s gonna die anyway.
[thunder rumbles]
[rain falling]
I want to give Kyle my heart.
This thing--
whatever it is--
you said he gets it
from the mother.
My heart’s fine.
And it could go on being fine
for the rest of your life.
(House)
Yeah.
It’s not like he’s gonna do
anything with it.
Well, you woke him up once.
Maybe someone will come up
with some other answer.
We’ve both seen breakthroughs
no one expected.
And ragged red fiber’s
treatable,
but not curable.
Even if he gets your heart,
there’s no guarantee.
He’s my kid.
No.
Did you really expect
a different answer?
We have arranged
transplants before
when a patient
is near death.
Except he isn’t
near death.
He’s saying, "Kill me
and cut out my heart."
Are you out of your mind?
Fine.
I’ll think of something else.
I’m sorry.
Wilson.
Get out.
No.
You’ve lied to the cops
enough for me.
Maybe I don’t wanna push this
till it breaks.
Pills are the simplest.
Hanging has less chance
of damaging the heart.
I’m okay with pain.
Strangulation is better
than breaking your neck.
Which means this’ll be slow.
I wouldn’t get to see him
even if we got
in the car right now
and broke the speed limit
driving back, would I?
No.
Tell him...
I don’t know
what to tell him.
[sighs]
Think it’s my turn
to ask a question, isn’t it?
I don’t think so.
’Cause you just asked me
that thing
about the speed limit.
What do you wanna know?
If you could hear one thing
from your father,
what would it be?
It wouldn’t help you.
Try me.
I’d want him to say...
[sighs]
"You were right.
You did the right thing."
Yeah.
It doesn’t help.
[laughing softly]
[slot machines clink]
Hi.
I’m Dr. Wilson.
I’m  M Schaeffer.
(Wilson)
I’m from Princeton.
My husband and I
and our three children
live in Philadelphia.
So, uh...
do you like to swing?
No.
Well, if you change your mind,
I’m in--
House. House!
Is it room 622?
642?
622.
Yeah.
Alibi.
I figured.
[heavy thump]
[tense music]
♪
They found an open bottle
of aspirin by the body.
Lucky he had a headache.
Reduced trauma to the heart
in transit.
Lucky.
That can’t be all.
Well, you got a heart
out of it.
How many organs do you want
from the guy?
I mean...
my father must have
said something.
He couldn’t just--
He must have given you
some kind of a message for me.
He said you were right.
You did the right thing.
Right about what?
What does that mean?
How would I know?
Know.
He’s your dad.
You know what I found
interesting about this case?
That it proved that people
can love unconditionally,
and you can tell yourself
it’s not true,
but you’ll just end up
in a hotel room
in Atlantic City
asking someone
to cut your heart out?
The hoagie.
You thought this guy
was emotionally confused
and that the hoagie
was just a mask
to hide his real feelings
towards his son.
It was.
Did you know Tritter
was talking to your team
while we were away?
Yeah.
And yet you moved
heaven and earth
to get him that mask
with mustard and prosciutto.
Which one of them
told you?
All of them.
Which means that none of them
said anything
I have to worry about.
Back to the hoagie.
You think that my addiction’s
out of hand.
Your need to be needed
is so strong
that you’ll give people
what they want,
what they need,
what they think they need.
I don’t think my enabling
is anything you should be
complaining about.
Yes, my name
is Dr. James Wilson.
Account number 835687.
The ATM says I’ve got zero--
What does that mean--
a hold?
[sighs]
Yeah, okay.
Thanks.
[sighs]
My accounts have been frozen
as part of a police
investigation.
They can’t keep
your money forever.
No, they can keep it
till I agree
to help send you to prison
for ten years.
[sighs]
You’re getting dinner.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com