[ Insect Buzzing ]
[ Louder Buzzing ]
Goddamn bugs.
Oh, shit.
รง Silencio !
[ Driver ]
Dejame hablar.
Oh, crap.
Well, Nick the Dick.
What a surprise.
Where you comin' from,
Nick ?
Fishin'
in Cuernavaca.
Sure you were.
What do you say we take
a look at your catch, huh ?
Come on.
Me, I would've
thrown 'em back.
Bajanse, todos.
Formen una linea aqui,
por favor.
So, Nick, what do you get ?
A hundred bucks a head ?
Two hundred ?
Hope you saved it all for
your lawyer, my friend,
because you are
gonna need it.
[ Brakes Screech ]
- We'll take it from here.
- Who the hell are you ?
I.N.S., Division Six.
Division Six ?
I never heard of
Division Six.
Really ?
Who you got your
money on, Dee ?
- Tough call, Kay.
- [ Chuckles ]
[ Speaks In Spanish ]
Okay.
Preoccupation in then either battles the.
Not only was organised is going to the
democracy louder the amusement we do.
Milwaukee.
He to.
They don't look at it.
When we fail at all.
The know I wasn't even up a.
- We've got a winner here, Dee.
- [ Chuckles ]
[ Agent Speaks In Spanish ]
If I watch sir.
- Sir, you can't just--
- Don't "sir" me, young man.
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
Soup and say they'll call me on our
eight the airport hour.
We're gonna have a little
chat with our friend here.
You fellas can hit the road.
[ Kay ]
Keep on protecting us
from the dangerous aliens.
You ever hear of
Division Six ?
There is no Division Six.
This is bullshit.
Hell, yeah.
Looks like you fell off
the bus in the wrong
part of town, amigo.
I'm gonna bet dollars to pesos
you're not from
anywhere near here.
- [ Roars ]
- Mikey ?
[ Alien Language ]
[ Continues ]
When'd they
let you out of jail ?
[ Continues ]
Political refugee,
right.
You know how many treaties
you just violated ?
[ Continues ]
One ?
Try seven.
[ Continues ]
That's enough, Mikey.
Hand me that head.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Continues ]
Put up your arms
and all your flippers.
[ Continues ]
[ Alien Continues Speaking
In Alien Language ]
[ Gasps ]
- [ Growling ]
- Ah, shit !
[ Snarling, Roaring ]
[ Kay ]
Dee, shoot him !
[ Snarling ]
[ Agent Screaming ]
- Dee !
- [ Screaming Continues ]
- [ Snarling ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Sighs ]
Th--
Th-- Th--
"That."
That wa-- wa--
Was not human, I know.
Looks like you got some
entrails on you, pal.
What the hell ?
The situation's
under control.
Calm down, please.
Give me your attention.
I'll be glad to tell you
what happened.
This is called
a neuralizer.
It's a gift from some
friends from out of town.
This red eye will
isolate the electronic
impulses in your brains--
more specifically,
the ones for memory.
That's good, fellas.
Give me a splay burn
around the perimeter...
with holes at
40, 60, and 80 meters
from right here.
Thank you.
[ Kay ]
That's good.
Thank you.
What in the hell
is going on ?
Excellent question.
And the answer you're
looking for lies right here.
Who are you, really ?
Really ?
I am just a figment
of your imagination.
[ Beeping, Zapping ]
Damn,
what a gullible breed.
I'm serious, fellas.
You're lucky to be alive
after a blast like that.
- What blast ?
- The underground gas main.
You fellas need to exercise
a lot more caution before
discharging your firearms.
Especially you.
Have yourselves checked out
with E.M.S. on the other side
of the hill before you leave.
I'm sorry about
back there.
It happens.
Didn't used to.
The spirit's willing, Kay,
but the rest of me--
[ Sighs ]
They're beautiful,
aren't they ?
What ?
The stars.
We never just look anymore.
[ Kay ]
No.
I'll tell you, Kay,
I will miss the chase.
[ Sighs ]
No, Dee, you won't.
Freeze !
N.Y.P.D. !
[ Panting ]
All yours, Edwards.
Freeze means stop !
Yo !
Whoa !
What the hell ?
All right.
Aw, come on !
- Aah !
- [ Passengers Screaming ]
It just be rainin'
black people in New York.
[ Grunting ]
Do you see this ?  Huh ?
N.Y.P.D. !
It means I will knock
your punk-ass down !
He's coming !
And when he gets here,
I'll arrest his ass too.
[ Electronic Beeping ]
Oh, you're tryin' to
catch a beat down, huh ?
[ Grunting ]
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Brakes Screech,
Horns Honk ]
[ Roaring ]
What's up ?
He's coming.
He's coming because I failed,
and now he'll kill me too.
Yeah well.
You're just pissin'
everybody off today, huh ?
You don't understand.
Your world's gonna end.
What the hell are you ?
Hey, watch that ledge.
Watch the ledge.
Look, come on down.
We'll get those eyes fixed.
Don't even worry about it.
Wait a minute.
Let me talk to you.
Hey !  Hey !
[ Body Thuds ]
[ Man ]
I work my butt off
to make a livin',
all I want is to come home
to a nice clean house...
with a nice fat steak
on the table,
but instead I get this.
It looks like poison.
Don't you take that away !
I'm eatin' that, damn it !
It is poison, isn't it ?
I swear to God, I would not
be surprised if it was,
the way you skulk around here
like a dog been hit too much,
or ain't been hit enough.
I can't make up my mind.
You're useless, Beatrice.
The only thing that pulls
its weight around here
is my goddamn truck !
Figures.
[ Screen Door Closes ]
What the heck is it, Edgar ?
Get your big butt
back in the house.
[ Screen Door Closes ]
[ Alien Voice ]
Place projectile weapon
on the ground.
You can have my gun
when you pry it from
my cold, dead fingers.
Your proposal
is acceptable.
[ Cracking Sound ]
[ Crunching ]
[ Footsteps ]
[ Grunting ]
Edgar, what on earth
was that ?
Sugar.
I've never seen
sugar do that.
Give me sugar.
In water.
More.
More !
[ Grunting ]
[ Gulping ]
[ Sighs Contentedly ]
Edgar, your skin
is hangin' off your bones.
[ Sloshing Sound ]
Oh, yeah.
There.
Is that better ?
[ Grunting ]
[ Mooing ]
"Perpetrator then blinked
two sets of eyelids."
You mean blinked
with both eyes ?
No, sir.
He blinked one set,
then he blinked
a completely different set.
You know,
like high beams
and low beams.
Was that before or after
he drew the weapon...
that you claimed evaporated
into a million pieces ?
After, sir.
And why is it that none
of the other officers saw
either of these two events ?
Some of the other officers
are soggy around
the midsection.
I guess that's why they
weren't able to keep up.
Edwards, if you were
half the man I am--
I am half the man
that you are.
Hey, what is your problem ?
My problem is you bein'
all up in my damn face.
I think he threw him
off the roof.
It may be you next.
- I want to talk to you.
- Ten minutes,
you take your best shot,
tough guy.
Take ten minutes
on a Stairmaster,
you pudgy bastard.
[ Sighs ]
I believe you.
Laurel Weaver,
Deputy Medical Examiner.
Find me at
the morgue on 26th.
Wait a minute.
- Hey, wait a minute.
- [ Kay ]  Excuse me.
You're Dr. Weaver
with the coroner's office
working on the John Doe, right ?
Yes, that's right.
Will you look
at this, please ?
[ Sighs ]
Some night, huh ?
Yeah, some night.
They were gills,
not eyelids.
Gills.
He was out of breath.
Who are you ?
Did he say anything
to you ?
Yeah, he said the world
was comin' to an end.
Did he say when ?
Would you recognize
that weapon of his
if you saw it again ?
Absolutely.
Come on,
let's take a ride.
Wait a minute.
I got tons of paperwork--
It's all done.
Good work, Edwards.
You really ran this
dude down on foot ?
That's tough, kid.
That's double tough.
[ Edwards ]
So, who exactly
are you with ?
F.B.I. ?
N.S.A. ?
[ Kay ]
I'm part of a bureau
that licenses, monitors...
and polices alien activity
on the planet Earth.
Yeah, whatever.
We're here.
This is where
we goin' ?
Yep.
This is Jack Jeebs' spot.
He buys from
chain snatchers.
He doesn't even
sell guns.
Really ?
Look, I'm gonna slide up
in here and I'm gonna
put my thing down.
But when I come back out,
I want some real answers.
Go.
Okay, go put
your thing down.
Officer Eduardo.
Hey, how did these
get here ?
I thought I turned these in
to the proper authorities.
The way I hear it, Jeebs,
you're into something hotter
than some stolen Rolexes.
That well.
I'm a huge crack dealer,
but I still work here
'cause I love the hours.
I'm talkin' about guns,
smart ass.  Weird ones.
Come on, Edwards.
What you see is what I got.
[ Door Opens ]
Why don't you show him
the imports, Jeebs ?
Hiya, Kay.
How are you ?
Show him the imports
right now.
I got out of
that business.
I hate it when you lie.
- Just hold on a second.
- I'm gonna count to three.
He'll do it, Jeebs.
That man does not look stable.
One, two...
He is just crazy
when he's like this.
He's always crazy.
Why don't you get a massage ?
Take a cruise--
three.
Drop the weapon.
- I warned him.
- Drop the weapon !
You warned him.
Don't make me kill you.
How.
[ Alien Voice ]
You insensitive prick !
Do you have any idea
how much that stings ?
Show us the merchandise
or you're gonna lose
another head.
[ Buzzer ]
Mr. Edwards ?
Right there,
the one in the middle.
You sold a reverberating
carbonizer with
mutate capacity...
to an unlicensed cephlapoid,
you piece of shit.
He looked all right to me.
It must've been for
an assassination.
Who's the target ?
I don't know.
Goddamn it,
Jeebs !
I don't know !
All right, let's
confiscate all of it.
And I want you on the next
transport off this rock...
or I'm gonna shoot you
where it don't grow back.
[ Turns Weapon Off ]
Yeah, and I'm gonna be back
to talk about them Rolexes.
[ Bell Jingles ]
Searching for a handle
on the moment ?
I can't help you.
The only comfort I can offer
is my promise...
that tomorrow morning,
you won't remember a thing.
That's not exactly some
shit you just forget.
[ Beeping ]
Have you ever seen
one of these, son ?
[ Kay Laughing ]
And so she looks over
at her husband,
then she sets it
back down in her lap
and she says,
"Honey, this one's
eating my popcorn."
[ Laughing Hysterically ]
Did you get it ?
"This one's eating my pop--"
Oh, gotta go.
Thanks for the
egg rolls, kid.
Wait a minute.
Who are you ?
See what I mean
about tequila ?
You're a very bright
young man, James, but you
need to lay off the sauce.
I'll see you bright
and early, 9:00.
Be there...
or be square.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Door Creaks ]
Well, well, well.
Movin' right in, are we ?
Think we own the place ?
I've got an eviction
notice for you boys.
Just what exactly do you
think you're doin' here ?
I'm takin' care
of your pest problem.
Pest problem ?
Pest ?
Yeah.  You got a hell
of an infestation.
You know, I've noticed
an infestation here.
Everywhere I look, in fact.
Nothin' but an undeveloped,
unevolved, barely conscious
pond scum,
totally convinced
of their own superiority...
as they scurry about
their short, pointless lives.
Well, yeah.
Don't you wanna
get rid of 'em ?
In the worst way.
[ Grunting ]
[ Fans Blowing ]
Help you ?
Yeah, this dude gave me
this card the other day--
Elevator.
[ Whirring Sound ]
You're late.
Sit down.
My name is Zed.
You're all here
because you're
the best of the best:
Marines, Air Force,
Navy SEALS,
Army Rangers, N.Y.P.D.
And we're looking
for one of you.
Just one.
What will follow
is a series of
simple tests...
for motor skills,
concentration, stamina.
I see we have
a question.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Maybe you already answered this,
but why exactly are we here ?
- Son ?
- Second Lieutenant Jake Jensen.
West Point.
Graduate with honors.
We're here because
you're looking for the best
of the best of the best, sir !
[ Chuckles ]
What's so funny, Edwards ?
Your boy,
Captain America over here.
"The best of the best
of the best, sir !
With honors."
Yeah, he's just
really excited...
and he has no clue
why we're here.
That's just--
That's very funny to me.
Y'all ain't laughin',
though.
Okay, let's get going.
[ Covers Ripped From Test Book ]
[ Horrible Scraping Sound ]
Ah.
Wanna get down on this ?
[ Alarm Sounding ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Door Opening ]
- [ Zed ]  Edwards,
what the hell happened ?
- Hesitated.
- May I ask why you felt little
Tiffany deserved to die ?
- She was the only one...
- that seemed dangerous, sir.
- How'd you come to
that conclusion ?
First I was gonna pop this guy
hangin' from the light.  Then
I realized he's workin' out.
How would I feel if somebody
come in the gym, bust me in my
ass while I'm on the treadmill ?
Then I saw this
snarling beast guy and I noticed
he had a tissue in his hand.
I'm realizing he's not snarling,
he's sneezing.
Ain't no real threat there.
Then I saw little Tiffany.
I'm thinking,
eight-year-old white girl,
middle of the ghetto,
bunch of monsters,
this time of night
with quantum physics books.
She about to
start some shit, Zed.
She's about eight years old.
Those books are way too advanced
for her.  If you ask me,
I say she's up to somethin'.
And to be honest,
I'd appreciate it if you
eased up off my back about it.
Or do I owe her
an apology ?
That was a good shot, though ?
Right ?
He's got a real problem
with authority.
So do I.
But this kid ran down
a cephlapoid.
On foot, boss.
That's gotta be
tough enough.
Let's hope you know
what you're doing.
[ Men Chattering ]
Gentlemen.
Congratulations.
You're everything
we've come to expect...
from years of
government training.
And now if you'll follow me,
we have one more test
to administer.  An eye exam.
Where you going ?
Yo.  Hey, man,
what the hell is all this ?
Back in the mid-1950s,
the government started
a little underfunded agency...
with the simple and laughable
purpose of establishing contact
with a race not of this planet.
[ Zed ]
...if you'll look directly
at the end of this device,
we'll administer
the eye test.
Everybody thought
the agency was a joke
except the aliens,
who made contact
March 2, 1961
outside New York.
There were nine of us
the first night.
Seven agents, one astronomer...
and one dumb kid who got lost
on the wrong back road.
Aw, you brought that
tall man some flowers.
This way.
They were a group of
intergalactic refugees.
Wanted to use the earth
as an apolitical zone
for creatures without a planet.
Did you ever see the movie
Casablanca ?
Mm-hmm.
Same thing,
'cept no Nazis.
Oh.
We agreed and we concealed
all the evidence
of their landing.
Uh-huh.  So, these are
real flying saucers and the
World's Fair was a cover-up ?
Why else would we
hold it in Queens ?
More non-humans arrive
every year and they
live among us in secret.
Uh, look.  I'm sorry.
Not to change the subject
or anything,
but when was the last time
you had a CAT scan ?
Six months ago.
It's company policy.
You should
make another appointment.
Look, tell your boy Zed I had
an absolutely wonderful time,
and thank you for everything.
But why don't you
show me the door ?
[ Sighing ]
All right.
I'm gonna get some coffee.
You want some ?
No, thank you.
I'm fine.
Okay.
[ Speaking Alien Language,
Laughing ]
How you doin', fellas ?
[ All ]
Hi, Kay.
That's not decaf,
is it ?
Viennese Cinnamon.
[ Kay ]
Don't tell me we only got that
powered cream.  I hate that.
[ Alien Speaking
Alien Language ]
Good.  Good.
You guys
getting along all right ?
[ Chattering In Alien ]
- [ Kay ]
Well, don't work too hard.
- [ All ]  Okay.
- So, you guys seen
the cahuengas on--
- Sure you don't want coffee ?
- [ Stuttering ]
- [ Aliens Continue Chattering ]
[ Aliens Laughing ]
[ Kay ]
All right, kid,
here's the deal.
At any given time there are
around 1,500 aliens
on the planet,
most of them
right here in Manhattan.
And most are decent enough.
They're just trying
to make a living.
Cab drivers.
Not as many
as you'd think.
Humans, for the most part,
don't have a clue.
They don't want or need one.
They're happy.
They think they have a...
good bead on things.
Uh, but why-why
the big secret ?
People are smart.
They can handle it.
A person is smart.
People are dumb, panicky,
dangerous animals,
and you know it.
Fifteen hundred years ago
everybody knew...
the earth was the center
of the universe.
Five hundred years ago
everybody knew
the earth was flat.
And fifteen minutes ago,
you knew that people were
alone on this planet.
[ Sighs ]
Imagine what
you'll know... tomorrow.
What's the catch ?
The catch ?
The catch is you will
sever every human contact.
Nobody will ever know
you exist anywhere.
Ever.
I'll give you till sunrise
to think it over.
Hey !
Is it worth it ?
Oh, yeah.
It's worth it.
If you're strong enough.
What's up, pops ?
All right, I'm in.
'Cause, look,
there's some next level shit
goin' on around here
and I'm with that.
But before y'all get to beamin'
me up, there's a couple of
things I want you to understand.
First off, you chose me,
so you recognize the skills.
And I don't want nobody callin'
me "son" or "kid" or "sport"
or nothin' like that.  Cool ?
Cool.  Whatever you say, slick.
But I need to tell you something
about your skills.
As of right now,
they mean precisely... dick.
Kay.
[ Woman On P.A. ]
Due to asteroid turbulence,
the 4:15 to Osiris
will be delayed.
[ Aliens Chattering ]
Purpose of trip ?
Diplomatic mission.
Duration of stay ?
Lunch.
Any fruits or
vegetables ?
[ Woman ]
The transport
from Xenderfloip has docked.
[ Speaking Alien ]
Please meet your party
outside the detainment area.
You wanna stay away
from that guy.  He's, uh--
[ Alien Growling ]
He's grouchy.
Three-hour delay
in customs...
after a trip of
17 trillion miles is
gonna make anybody cranky.
You know what I mean ?
Wh-What branch of the
government do we report to ?
Well, none.  They ask
too many questions.
Who pays for all this ?
We hold the patents
on a few gadgets we confiscated
from out-of-state visitors.
Um, Velcro,
microwave ovens, liposuction.
This is a fascinating
little gadget.
It's gonna replace CD's soon.
Guess I'll have to buy
the "White" album again.
Oh.  That is a lot of fun.
It's a universal translator.
We're not even
supposed to have it,
and I'll tell you why.
Human thought is
so primitive it's looked upon
as an infectious disease...
in some of
the better galaxies.
[ Device Beeping ]
That kinda makes you proud,
doesn't it ?  Huh ?
Hey, what's this thin--
Whoo !  Oh !
- [ Crowd Shouting ]
- Oh !  Okay, just be calm !
Just be--  Relax !
Okay ?  Ooh, watch your heads !
Somebody get him
some ice !  Ooh.
Look out !  Just move
when it's comin' at you !
Oh, damn.
Um, um, I'm gonna
pay for that !
- [ Woman Screams ]
- Oh !
This thing caused
the 1977 New York blackout.
Practical joke
by the Great Attracter.
He thought it was funny as hell.
Sorry, y'all.
It was a accident.
Sorry.
Observation.
The heart of
our little endeavor.
Meet the twins.
"Blblup" and Bob.
This map shows the location
of every registered alien
on earth at any given time.
Some of them
under constant surveillance.
Everyone on those screens
is an alien.
In public, they're as normal
as you are but in private--
Well.
- You'll get the idea.
- Oh, man.
Doesn't make any sense,
does it ?
Well, no--  It makes
perfect sense.
When I was in third grade,
everybody told me
I was crazy,
but I knew our teacher
had to be fro-from, like
Venus or somethin' like that.
Ms. Edelson.
Jupiter, actually.
Well, one of the moons.
[ Woman ]
Revolve.  Class !
Be quiet and pay attention !
If I have to tell you
one more time--
[ Zed ]
Edwards !  Let's put it on.
- Put what on ?
- The last suit
you'll ever wear.
[ Zed ]
You will dress only in attire
specially sanctioned...
by MIB Special Services.
You'll conform
to the identity we give you,
eat where we tell you,
live where we tell you.
From now on, you'll have no
identifying marks of any kind.
You will not stand out
in any way.
Your entire image is crafted...
to leave no lasting memory
with anyone you encounter.
Ow !
You are a rumor,
recognizable only...
as deja vu,
and dismissed just as quickly.
You don't exist.
You were never even born.
Anonymity is your name.
Silence your native tongue.
You are no longer
part of the system.
You are above the system.
Over it.  Beyond it.
We're "them."
We're "they."
We are the Men in Black.
[ Jay ]
You know what the difference is
between you and me ?
I make this look good.
Gonna go for a little ride,
you and me.
I'll put you down here
for just a minute,
then Daddy'll be right back.
[ Meowing ]
[ Tires Squealing ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Meows ]
Okay.  We're ready to go
for a little ride.
We're gonna meet
one of Daddy's friends
and you're gonna like him.
Okay, let's see.
Bee !
We've got the deposed
sur-prefect of Singalee...
touching down in the forest
outside Portland tonight.
Humanoid ?
You wish.  Bring a sponge.
[ Chuckles ]
And here.  Red letter
from last night.
We had an unauthorized
landing somewhere
in upstate New York.
Kay, keep your ears
opened on this one.
We're not hosting an
intergalactic kegger here.
[ Alarm Beeping ]
Well, well, well.
We got a skimmer.
Landed alien out of zone.
Who is it ?
Redgick.
He's not cleared to
leave Manhattan, but he's
way outta town right now.
Stuck on the
New Jersey Turnpike.
Why don't you take Junior here
with you.  This is a good one
for him to warm up on.
Go get 'em, tiger.
[ Alarm Continues ]
[ Jay Mocking ]
We're not hosting
an intergalactic kegger.
[ Chuckles ]
Zed.  He just--
Unlimited technology
from the whole universe,
and we cruise around
in a Ford P.O.S.
- Fasten your seat belt.
- See, now we got to work
on your people skills.
You know, you'd get a much
better reaction if you were
a little more polite.
- Fasten your seat belt, please.
- Whoa, that was good.
- Did you hurt yourself--
- [ Tires Screech, Motor Revs ]
[ Yells ]
Oh, the red button there, kid.
Don't ever, ever
touch the red button.
Oh !
Ooh.
[ Tires Screech ]
All right, Pop,
that'll be $72, there.
[ Woman's Voice, Indistinct ]
Okay, sweetie, let me pay
the impolite driver.
[ Tires Screech ]
[ Sighs, Grunts ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Meows ]
[ Speaking Alien Language ]
You are free.
I guess you are on the that gives me
great structures are not touching shoot
purchase hey john keats costs cheat day.
Pottery sculpture yeah that's he adds
garage question correctly me that.
The florida jupiter.
[ Bell Rings ]
Six is up !
Where is Ivan ?
[ Edgar ]
Gave him a break.
[ Speaking Alien Language ]
[ Grunts ]
You can kill us both,
but you will not
find the Galaxy.
Oh, you're right
about one thing.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Moans ]
- [ Yells ]
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Edgar Yells ]
- [ Meows ]
- [ Hisses ]
- [ Yells ]
[ Meows, Hisses ]
You're not goin'
anywhere, pal.
[ Grunts ]
[ Yelling, Chattering ]
What's goin' on, man ?
[ Grunts ]
Hey, hey,
hey, easy !
[ Chattering ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Growls ]
Like to see your license
and registration, please.
Like to see your other license
All right, your resident alien
card has you restricted
to the island of Manhattan.
- Where are you goin', Redgie ?
- Well, it's my wife.  She's--
Well, look.
[ Crying, Squealing ]
[ Kay ]
Oh, all right.
Okay, no big deal.
Okay.  You come with me, Redge.
[ Crying,
Squealing Continue ]
[ Blows ]
And, um, and you
handle this.
- What ?  Me ?
- Yeah, it's easy.
You just catch.
Are you sure he knows
what he's doing ?
He does it all the time.
Let the man work.
[ Whispering ]
Hey.
Um.  Okay,
uh, yeah.
[ Crying, Grunting ]
[ Blows ]
[ Screaming ]
Ooh !  Kay !
Oh, damn, man !
Some--  Kay !
Something's peekin' !
[ Screaming, Grunting ]
Croagg the Midwife's at 54th
and Madison.
[ Screaming Continues ]
You're headed out of town,
Redgie.  What's goin' on ?
Well, we're
meeting someone.
Who are you meeting ?
Well, it's a ship.
A ship ?  I didn't see
a departure clearance for today.
You didn't ?
No.
Well, it's an emergency.
What--
You're doin' fine, ace.
What kind of emergency ?
What's the rush to get off
the planet all of a sudden ?
Excuse me, Miss.
We just don't like
the neighborhood anymore.
Kay !
It's just some of the, uh,
new arrivals.
What new arrivals ?
Have anything to do with
the crasher from last night ?
Excuse me, Miss.
[ Screams ]
[ Grunts, Whimpers ]
[ Jay ]
Oh, man.
Oh, man.  Oh.
Oh, Kay, look.
- Oh, man.
- [ Laughs ]
Congratulations, Redge,
it's a... squid.
[ Jay ]
Kay, man.
[ Laughs ]
You know, it's actually
kind of--
[ Hacks, Giggles ]
[ Spits ]
Cute.
[ Car Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Kay Sighs ]
Anything about that
seem unusual to you ?
What would scare Redgick
so badly that he'd risk
a warp jump with a newborn ?
We'll check
the hot sheets.
[ Engine Starts ]
These are the hot sheets ?
Best investigative
reporting on the planet.
Go ahead.
Read the New York Times
if you want to.
They get lucky sometimes.
Thanks, Manny.
Cannot believe
you're lookin' for tips
in the supermarket tabloids.
Not lookin' for.
Found.
Wait a minute.
Slow down.
Why ?
Give her time
to get the wrong impression.
Makes things go a lot smoother.
- Can I help you gentlemen ?
- Uh, yes, ma'am.
I'm Special Agent Manheim.
This is Special Agent Black,
F.B.I.  We'd like to talk
to you about your visitor.
You here to make fun
of me too ?
No, ma'am.
We at the FBI do not have
a sense of humor we're
aware of.  May we come in ?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Lemonade ?
Oh, yes, please.
The chief of police himself
come up to the house...
and did a full out
professional investigation.
Took a police report and writ
down everything I said,
from A to Z, not believing
one thing I said.
Sort of pokin' fun
at me.
And they asked me, "If he was
murdered, how was he able
to walk back in the house ?"
And I gotta admit to you that
that one got me sort of stumped.
But I'll tell you somethin'
right now.  I know Edgar,
and that wasn't Edgar.
It's like somethin'
was wearin' Edgar.
Like a... like a suit.
An... Edgar suit.
[ Laughs, Cries ]
Dude was that ugly
before he was a alien.
[ Laughing Continues ]
I'm sorry.
Go on.
[ Chuckles, Sniffles ]
Anyway.
I come to,
and he's gone.
- Did he say anything ?
- Yes.
He asked me
for some water.
- Some, uh, sugar water.
- Sugar water ?
Yeah, I remember
that right.
Because I thought that
that was odd.  That he asked me
for sugar water...
and not lemonade
or ice water or...
regular water
or tap water.
All right, Beatrice.
There was no alien.
The flash of light
you saw in the sky
was not a UFO.
Swamp gas from a weather
balloon was trapped
in a thermal pocket...
and it refracted
the light from Venus.
W-Wa-Wait a minute.
So you just flash that thing,
it erases her memory
and y-you just make up
a new one ?
A standard
issue neuralizer.
And that weak-ass story
is the best you can
come up with ?
All right.  On a more personal
note, Beatrice, Edgar ran off
with an old girlfriend.
You're gonna go stay with
your mom a couple of nights.
You're gonna get
over it and decide
you're better off.
Well, yeah, you know,
'ca-'cause h-he never
appreciated you anyway.
In fact, you know what ?
You kicked him out.
And now that he's gone,
you gonna go in town,
you go to Bloomingdales,
you find yourself
some nice dresses.
Get yourself some shoes.
You know, find somewhere,
maybe, you could get a facial.
And, uh, oh.  Hire a decorator
to come in here quick,
'cause... damn !
Yo, Kay, when do
I get my own...
flashy, little memory
messer-upper thingy ?
Up.
Please, not green.
Oh, damn.
I don't suppose you know
what kind of alien life-form...
leaves a green spectral trail
and craves sugar water, do you ?
Oh, wait.  That was on
"Final Jeopardy" last night.
Damn, Alex said--
Zed, we have a bug.
So... what ?
We don't like bugs ?
Bugs thrive
on carnage, tiger.
They consume,
infest, destroy,
live off the death
and destruction
of other species.
You were stung
as a child, weren't you ?
Listen, kid.
Imagine a giant cockroach
with unlimited strength,
a massive
inferiority complex
and a real short temper...
is tear-assing
around Manhattan Island
in a brand-new Edgar suit.
That sound like fun ?
What's the move ?
With the bug in town,
we'll watch the morgues.
Where do you want
contestant number three ?
Just leave it there.
What's with the cat ?
Oh, the cat.
There's a problem with the cat.
Sign here.
What's the problem
with the cat ?
It's your problem.  Heh-heh.
I hate the living.
Shall we ?
Oh, my God.
Whoa, buddy,
what are you ?
Subject was approximately
112 degrees at time of autopsy,
indicating an increase
in body temperature.
Examiner tried to verify this
rectally only to find
the subject was without rectum,
which is,
needless to say, really--
Weird.  I'm Dr. Leo Manville,
Department of Public Health.
This is Dr. White.
[ Medical Examiner Scoffs ]
You boys must not have
much of a home life.
We watch the morgues carefully.
Do you have something
unusual around here ?
I'd say so.
Triple homicide.
The first body I opened up
was pretty normal, except he
was broken in half.
But when I opened up
the other two--
Well, let me show you.
There's a skeletal structure
unlike anything
I've ever seen before.
[ Kay ]
I'll have a look
at this one.
Dr. White, why don't you
and Dr. Weaver check out
the other body ?
This way, Doctor.
This one's
even stranger.
I did a full laparotomy.
I started with the lesser
curvature of the stomach,
but we could start with
the gastroesophageal junction.
Let's start
wherever you started at.
Okeydokey.
Oh.
[ Meowing ]
- That your cat ?
- Guess it is now.
It came in with the body.
Okay.  Dive right in.
I'm sure
he won't mind.
[ Groaning ]
You have
really pretty eyes.
Thank you.
You feel that ?
Where the pyloric
junction would be ?
Push it aside.
Notice anything strange ?
[ Groaning ]
Stomach, liver, lungs.
Nope.  All fine.
Doctor,
they're all missing.
Of course.  That's obviously
the first thing I noticed.
What I was pointing out
is the fact that there
are no, um, pieces...
of them left.
Yeah, you know,
so they're intact...
wherever they are
whole somewhere.
That we can
be sure of.
Have we met before ?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm having the strangest
feeling of deja vu.
Yeah, me too.
Really ?
You wanna know
what I really think,
but don't tell that guy.
He looks like he's
under enough stress.
See, I don't think
this body's really a body.
I think it's some kind
of transport unit
for something else.
The question is, what ?
Mm-hmm.
This freaking you out ?
Nah.  [ Scoffing ]
Nah, girl.
You know what I like
to do sometimes
when it's really late ?
No.
Dr. White ?
Um, excuse me.
Ugh !
What do you think ?
Very interesting.
She got a real "Queen of
the Undead" thing goin'.
No, the body.
Great body.
The dead body.
Oh.
You gonna have to go
look at that thing.
You recognize him ?
Yeah, he looks like the big guy
I saw down at headquarters,
only a little deader.
What do you think
killed him ?
Bug ?
Dr. White.
You're up, slugger.
Oh.
Look at this.
[ Jay ]
What the hell
is that ?
[ Beeping, Hissing ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Labored Breathing ]
Must...
[ Sighing ]
to prevent...
contest.
It's okay.
What are you
trying to say ?
- To prevent--
- To prevent... struggle ?
[ Sighing ]
No.  To prevent--
- War ?
- War.
The galaxy...
is on...
Orion's...
be-- be--
What is word ?
[ Labored Breathing ]
[ Jay ]
Bed ?
Belt ?  Orion's belt ?
[ Meowing ]
[ Sighing ]
"To prevent war, the galaxy
is on Orion's belt."
What the hell does that mean ?
[ Sighing ]
Dr., um--
Whatever.
Come here.
Dr. Whatever ?
You guys aren't really from
the Department of Health,
are you ?
Rosenberg--
Oh, damn.
[ Kay ]
The Arquillians
are not gonna like this.
This guy was one
of the royal family.
I knew it.
This is an alien, and you guys
are from some government agency
trying to keep it under wraps.
He said,
"To prevent war, the galaxy
is on Orion's belt."
This makes total sense.
How else do you
explain New York ?
The other day,
I was in this cab,
and this guy was--
"Galaxy on Orion's belt"
doesn't make sense.
That's what the little dude
inside the big dude's head said,
right ?  Right after--
Damn, man !  You did
the flashy thing already.
Whoever you guys are,
show me I.D. if you're
gonna be in the morgue.
Of course, young lady.
Have a look at this
for me, please.
Would you stop that ?
What ?
That thing is gonna give her
brain cancer or something.
Never hurt her before.
We gotta get
the doors closed.
Special services
will be here any minute.
"Never hurt her before" ?
How many times have you
"flashy thinged"
that poor woman ?
Couple.
You're not worried about
no long-term damage ?
A little.
Have you ever
flashy-thinged me ?
No.
I ain't playin'
with you, Kay.
Have you ever
flashy-thinged me ?
No.
I think I should be in charge
of the flashy memory thing
department.
Not while I'm around, ace.
You won't be happy till you
fricassee somebody's brain out.
We got two dead aliens
and a deputy medical examiner
who needs a new memory.
Yes, sir.
Make it
a happy memory.
[ Shouting, Banging ]
[ Grunting, Screaming ]
[ Crunching ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Edgar Growling ]
Where is it ?
[ Sighing ]
[ Jay ]
Hey, Zed.
Doesn't anybody ever get
any sleep around here ?
The twins keep us
on Centaurian time.
It's a 37-hour day.
Would.
Give it a few months.
You'll get used to it, or you'll
have a psychotic episode.
Here's Orion.  It's a grouping
of the brightest stars
in the northern sky.
And here's Orion's belt.
That's what
the little guy said.
"To prevent war,
the galaxy is on
Orion's belt."
Junior, there are no galaxies
on Orion's belt.
The belt is just
these three stars.
Galaxies are huge.
They're made up
of billions of stars.
You heard wrong.
Whatever, man.
I know what I heard.
Pretty lady.
[ Beeping ]
Uh-huh.  Okay.
That grumpy-guy story's
startin' to come into focus
a little bit here.
So you were the guy in
that picture you showed me
with the flowers.
Yeah.
And I take it she never
got those flowers.
She ever get married
or anything ?
No.
Well, you know
what they say.
"It's better to have loved
and lost than never
to have loved at all."
Try it.
[ Zed ]
Kay.
Take a look
at this.
They're all leaving.
We've had 12 jump
in the last hour.
Redgick was
just the first.
What the hell
do they know
that we don't ?
Why does a rat
desert a ship ?
Give me Lem Sat Four,
please, with a proton
induction thermoscan.
[ Kay ]
Thank you.  Okay.
Lem Sat 18.
All right.
Four thousand.
[ Kay ]
That's an Arquillian
battle cruiser.
And we've got
a dead Arquillian prince.
[ Indistinct Arquillian
Radio Transmission ]
[ Kay ]  Speak of the devil.
They sound pissed.
Boys, translate that.
Step on it.
Get down to Rosenberg's
jewelry store and see
what you can turn up.
Kay ?
Give the kid a weapon.
A Series Four de-atomizer.
That's what
I'm talkin' about.
Noisy cricket.
Hey, Kay.  Nah, nah.
Come on, man.
You get
a Series Four de-atomizer,
I get a little midget cricket ?
Ooh !  Kid !
Feel like I'm gonna break
this damn thing.
[ Snorting ]
[ Hiccuping, Gagging ]
- [ Grunting ]
- [ Machinery Whirring ]
Hey, this is
my truck !
Yeah, and make sure
you tell 'em that
down at the impound.
[ Grunting ]
Please.
Who breaks into
a jewelry store and
leaves all the jewels ?
Somebody not looking
for jewelry.
This guy had
a serious crush
on his cat.
[ Gunshot ]
Get down !
Ahh !
Eeee !
That's him !
That's the bug
in the Edgar suit.
- [ Gunshot ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Screaming ]
We do not discharge our weapons
in view of the public !
Man, we ain't got time
for this cover-up bullshit !
I don't know whether or not
you've forgotten, but there's
a alien battle cruiser--
There's always an alien battle
cruiser or a Korilian death ray
or intergalactic plague...
that's about to wipe out life
on this miserable planet.
The only way people get on
with their happy lives is,
they do not
know about it.
And don't worry about the bug.
He's not leavin' town.
We got his ship.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, ladies
and gentlemen, uh--
Zed, we need a containment crew
on McDougal Street,
south of Houston.
[ Chuckles ]  Containment may be
a moot point, old friend.
The exodus continues.
It's like the party's over,
and the last to leave...
gets stuck with the check.
[ Aliens Chattering ]
[ Groans ]
You sorry little ingrates !
Ahh !  [ Shouting In
Alien Language ]  ...Zed !
[ Raucous Laughter ]
โชโช [ Singing "Star-Spangled
Banner" In Alien Language ]
[ Kay ]  What about
the Arquillians ?
We've only translated
part of the message so far:
"Deliver the galaxy."
They don't want much,
do they ?
Oh, it gets better.
They're holding us
responsible.
[ Grunting ]
Where do you keep
your dead ?
I don't have any dead.
[ Grunts ]
Where ?
[ Choking ]
I-I don't know.
Uh, th-the city morgue ?
[ Grunts ]
That's three
for a dollar !  Sir !
Well, some light--
Some light refracted, uh,
off of Venus...
into some swamp gas,
and that's what made the, um--
[ Kay ]
All right, kid.
E-Excuse me.  What's up ?
The Arquillians want the galaxy,
whatever that means.
We need help--
a professional,
somebody
with years of experience
in intergalactic politics.
I just hope the little prick
hasn't skipped town.
[ Man On P.A. ]
May I have your attention,
please ?  Thank you.
If you will gather over here.
That's right.  Move in closer.
That's good.  Thanks.
If you'll look right here,
I'd appreciate it.  Thank you.
That's the worst disguise ever.
That guy's definitely an alien.
***
- You busy, Frank ?
- Sorry, can't talk now.
My flight's leavin'--
Whoa !  Get your paws off me !
Call the pound.
We got a stray.
- The dog owes my friend money.
- Arquillians and bugs, Frank.
What do you know ?
- I know nothin'.  [ Yelping ]
- Not a thing ?  Okay.
[ Yelping Continues ]
Stop it !  Stop it !  Stop it !
Okay !  Okay !
Rosenberg wasn't
some two-bit Arquillian.  He was
the guardian of a whole galaxy.
- Th-They thought he'd
be safe here on Earth.
- And the bug had other plans.
The galaxy is the best source
for subatomic energy
in the universe.
If the bugs
get their claws on it,
kiss the Arquillians good-bye.
Ask about the belt.
Rosenberg
said something about Orion's
belt.  What's he talkin' about ?
Beats me.
Beat you ?  Okay.
[ Yelping ]
No !  No !  No !
Stop it !  Ow !
Uh, they're rehearsing
a ventriloquist act.
The galaxy is here !
What do you mean "here" ?
A galaxy's hundreds of millions
of stars.  How is it here ?
You humans--
when are you gonna learn
that size doesn't matter ?
Just 'cause something's
important, doesn't mean
it's not very, very small.
How small ?
Tiny.  Like the size
of a marble or a jewel.
If you'll excuse me,
I gotta be walked
before my flight.
All right,
get outta here.
If the galaxy's here,
it's not on Orion's belt.
[ Barking ]
[ Meows ]
Kay.
[ Gasps ]
[ Meows ]
[ Purring ]
Boy, when you
want attention--
Orion ?
That's a pretty name.
What's this ?
Wow.
[ Grunts ]
[ Dings ]
[ Dinging Continues ]
[ Man ]
Okay.
Yes, good.  Thank you.
Thank you for making sure
the bell works.
What's up,
Farmer John ?
Ohh, a man
came in here earlier.
- A dead man.
- And that means what to me ?
He was a very dear friend
of mine.
I believe he had
an animal with him.
It was a gift I gave him.
A pet cat.
Means worlds to me.
[ Clears Throat ]
I'd like to have it back.
I'm gonna need a picture I.D.,
written proof of ownership
of the cat,
notarized proof of kinship
with... the deceased.
Don't do that.
Do what ?
Don't do it.
Oh, man.
[ Growling ]
[ Tires Screech ]
Kay, why don't you
let me handle this one ?
What ?
All we gotta do is
go in and get a cat.
It's not that hard.
If you go in there, you're gonna
lay your Jack Webb on her,
start flashin' your brain ray.
***
She don't need you flashin' away
half her med school classes.
Five minutes.
Two minutes.
Where's the animal ?
I told you, I don't know.
Let's see if we can
find it.
[ Yelling,
Grunting ]
- [ Bell Dinging ]
- [ Jay ]  Hello ?
Hello ?
How ya doin' ?
Hello.
I'm Sergeant Friday
from the 26th precinct.
Uh, a cat came in
with a corpse the other day.
"Orion" on the name tag.
- Yes, that's right.
- Right.  Uh, well,
this cat is a, a witness
in a murder case.
I'm gonna need to take him,
ask him a few questions.
- I don't know where
the cat is right now.
- Oh, you don't ?
No, but maybe you could take me
with you instead.
Damn, you do start fast,
don't you ?
I'd really like to go
with you... now.
Uh-huh.  And, uh,
exactly why is that ?
Look, stud, you're really
not getting this.
There's something I need you
to help me with.
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
- Freeze it, bug.
- Christ, you are thick !
- How was I to know ?
- Did I have to sing it
for you ?
- If you weren't comin' on
like some drunken prom date--
- That is so typical.
- A woman shows the slightest
hint of sexual independence--
- Shut up !
- Let her go, shit-eater.
- Listen, monkey boy.
Compared to you, I'm on the top
rung of the evolutionary ladder.
So can it, all right ?
Show me your face,
and I'll cure
all your ills.
Ever pull wings off a fly ?
Ya care to see the fly
get even ?
How far do you think you're
gonna get without your ship--
that piece of space trash ?
[ Alien ]  Put your weapons
down !
[ Kay ]
Never gonna happen.
- [ Jay ]  It's okay, Laurel.
- How is it okay ?
I'm sayin'
i-it's gonna be okay.
Don't bet on it,
meat sack.
[ Gasps ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting, Screaming ]
Let me go !
- Ah, take me here.
- No way.
- Take me !
- [ Tires Squealing ]
Come back !
He's in a cab !
Don't move !  Don't move !
Don't move !
Hey, man, what ?
Whoa !
[ Tires Squealing ]
He's not leaving the planet
in a cab.  Let's go.
Come with me.
Put up a bio-net all
the way around Manhattan.
If it's not human,
I don't want it
to leave this island.
Yes, sir.
What do we hear
from our friends upstairs ?
"Deliver the galaxy."
We've got
the bug's ship.
He's gotta
be looking
for a way out.
[ Alarm Sounding ]
[ Computer ]
Warning.
Protonic fusion detection.
Warning.  Protonic fusion
detection.
What the hell are they
shootin' at us for ?
Arquillian battle rules.
[ Kay ]
First we get an ultimatum,
then a warning shot,
and then we have
a galactic standard week
to respond.
"A galactic standard week" ?
How the hell long is that ?
One hour.
Then what ?
[ Alarm Sounding ]
[ Jay ]
Oh, that's bullshit.
To keep the bugs
from getting it,
the Arquillians will
destroy that galaxy.
[ Zed ]
And whatever planet
it's on.
You're talking about us.
[ Chuckles ]
Sucks, huh ?
I'm pulling up
the location...
of every
interstellar vehicle
within 100 miles.
Already did.
Frank the Pug
took the last ship.
We got Snedens Landing
and Throg's Neck.
They're all gone.
Atlantic City ?
Adios.  Gone.
All right.
Bayonne.
Gone.
All right.  There's
Three Mile Island.
Gone.
Yo.
Staten Island ?
Gone, thank God.
Fellas.
If that bug gets off
the planet with that galaxy,
we're all bug food.
Hey, old guys !
Do those still work ?
[ Edgar ]
You're comin' with me.
[ Laurel ]  What ?
It's a long trip.
I'll need a snack.
Whoa !
[ Screams ]
Wait a minute.
You're taking the tunnel ?
You know a better way
to get to Queens ?
Thing's gonna be packed.
[ Tires Squealing ]
- Do you remember
the little red button ?
- Yeah.
Push the little
red button.
And you may wanna
put on a seat belt.
[ Jay ]
Kay !
[ Screaming ]
[ Groaning ]
You're much too tense.
You're a young man.
You need to relax.
Learn to take some joy
in your work.
Do you like music ?
โช [ Rock 'n' Roll ]
Man !
That's better.
โช Left my home
in Norfolk, Virginia โช
โช California on my mind โช
โช I straddled that Grayhound
and rode him into Raleigh โช
โช And all across
Caroline โช
โช Somebody help me
get out of Louisiana โช
โช [ Continues ]
โช There are people there
who care a little 'bout me โช
โช And they won't let
the poor boy down โช
All right, now.
Aw, shit !
Aw, damn !
[ Humming ]
[ Jay ]
Kay.  Kay !
You do know
Elvis is dead, right ?
No, Elvis is not dead.
He just went home.
โช Swing low, chariot
Come down easy โช
โช Take me
to the terminal zone โช
โช Cut your engine
and cool your wings โช
โช And let me make it
to the telephone โชโช
[ Dinging, Ringing ]
[ Laurel Groans ]
You don't want
to eat me.
I'm a very
important person
on my planet.
Like a queen.
A goddess, even.
There are those
who worship me.
I'm not telling you this
to try to impress you.
I'm just letting you know
it could start a war.
Good !  War--
That means more food
for my family,
all 78 million
of 'em.
That's a lot
of mouths to feed,
your highness.
You're a wonderful dad,
but I'm staying here !
- [ Groans ]
- Oh !
Now, that's
what I'm talkin' about.
Roaches check in.
But they don't
check out.
Warning.  Eight minutes
to the destruction
of earth.
Eight minutes
to destruction.
[ Crowd Cheering ]
We'll use pulsar level five
with the sub-sonic
implosion factor.
What ?
Just shoot the damn thing
on the count of three.
One, two, three !
Oh, you idiots !
You don't get it.
I've won.
It's over.
You milk suckers !
You don't matter.
In fact, in a few seconds,
you won't even be matter.
You're under arrest
for violating sections
4153 of the Tycho Treaty.
[ Jay ]
So hand over whatever
galaxy you might be carrying...
and step away from your
busted-ass vehicle,
and put your hands on your head.
Oh, oh.
Let's see.
I put my hands...
on,
on my head.
Like this ?
Kay.
[ Snarling ]
[ Roaring ]
That did not go at all
the way I planned.
Whatever happens,
don't let him get
on the second ship.
What ?  What are you
talking about ?
Keep him on this planet.
Kay--  Kay,
where are you goin' ?
I'm gonna
get my gun back.
[ Kay ]
Hey !  Hey, bug !
Wait a minute.
I'm talking to you.
You know how many
of your kind I've swatted
with a newspaper ?
You're nothing but a smear
on the sports page to me,
you slimy, gut-sucking
intestinal parasite !
Eat me.
Eat me !
[ Growling ]
Kay !  Kay !
[ Roaring ]
Hey !
What's up ?
You're just gonna
eat and run, huh ?
What about dessert ?
[ Groans ]
Whoa.
That's it ?
Where you goin' ?
This party's just
gettin' started.
Where you goin' ?
[ Snarls ]
Let me tell you
somethin'.
There's only one way
off of this planet, baby,
and that's through me.
[ Panting ]
- [ Snarling ]
- Yo !
[ Yelling ]
[ Snarling ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Branches Snap,
Laurel Screams ]
Hey !
Where you goin' ?
Why you runnin',
huh ?
I'm still standin'.
Come on, bring it !
- [ Loud Crunch ]
- [ Snarling ]
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry.
Was that your auntie ?
[ Snarling ]
Then that must mean
that that's your uncle
then, huh ?
[ Loud Crunch ]
Oh, you know
y'all look alike.
[ Growling,
Roaring ]
[ Chuckles ]
Well, well.
Big bad bug got a bit
of a soft spot, huh ?
- [ Crunch ]
- [ Snarling ]
See, what I can't understand
is why you gotta come down here
bringin' all this ruckus.
Snatchin' up galaxies
and everything.
My attitude is,
don't start nothin',
won't be nothin'.
[ Growling ]
You need to ease up
out my face before
something bad happen to you.
[ Electronic Whining ]
Too late.
[ Both Groaning ]
Ugh !
[ Beeping ]
Zed, call the Arquillians.
Tell them we have
the galaxy.
You got it,
friend.
Ugh.  Goin' to get
your gun back, huh ?
I like this gun.
Yeah, well, while you
was in there playin' around,
I was down here
doin' all the work.
You know, first I had
to bean him in the head
with this big rock.
Then I was gonna hit him
with this two-by-four.
He kicked me.
You know, it hurt.
But then I got
to-to the fire, you know,
I was "yah !" with the fire.
Not bad for your
second day of work,
is it ?
This definitely rates
about a 9.0 on my
weird-shit-o-meter.
Should have been here
for the Zeronion
migration in 1968.
Whoa.
I guess you weren't
even alive in '68.
Interesting job
you guys have.
Kay, um, look, I know
we got these rules
and everything,
but I was thinking,
she did help us
bust that bug,
and maybe we didn't
have to flashy thing her.
Kay, come on, man.
Wh-Who's she gonna tell ?
She hang out
with all dead people.
It's not for her.
It's for me.
[ Chuckling ]
What ?
They're beautiful,
aren't they ?
Stars.
I mean, I never look at them
anymore, but they actually
are quite, uh...
beautiful.
Uh...
Kay, you're frightening
your partner.
I haven't been training
a partner.  I've been
training a replacement.
Wait a minute, Kay.
I cannot do this job
by myself.
Hey, guys, my apartment
isn't anywhere near here.
It's not even
on the same island.
[ Clicking ]
Days.
Months.
Years.
Always face it
forward.
Kay.
I've just been down
the gullet...
of an interstellar
cockroach, kid.
That's one
of a hundred memories
that I don't want.
See you around, Jay.
[ Beep,
Electronic Whirr ]
No, you won't.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Laurel ]
Hey, Jay.
Zed called.
The high Consulate
from Solaxiant Nine...
wants floor seats
for the Knicks-Bulls game.
All right.  Let's put in
a call to Dennis Rodman.
He's from that planet.
Rodman ?
You're kidding.
Nope.
Not much
of a disguise.
โช [ Dance Beat ]
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช It's the M.I.B.s โช
โช Here come the M.I.B.s โช
โช Men in black โช
โช Here come
men in black โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช The good guys dress in black
remember that โช
โช Just in case
we're ever face to face
and make contact โช
โช The title held by me
M.I.B. โช
โช 'Cause what you think you saw
you did not see โช
โช So don't blink, "B"
What was there is now gone โช
โช Put the black suit
with the black Ray-Bans on โช
โช Walk in shadow
Move in silence โช
โช Guard against
extraterrestrial violence โช
โช But yo we ain't on
no government list โช
โช We straight don't exist
no names and no fingerprints โช
โช Saw somethin' strange
Watch your back โช
โช 'Cause you never quite know
where the M.I.B.s is at โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Men in black โช
โช Galaxy defenders โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Men in black โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช From the deepest
of the darkest of night โช
โช On the horizon
bright lightnin' โช
โช To sight tight, Camera zoom
on the impending doom โช
โช But then like boom
black suits
filled the room up โช
โช With a quickness
Talk with the witnesses โช
โช Hipnotizer
Normalizer โช
โช Vivid memories
turn to fantasies โช
โช Ain't no M.I.B.s
can I plead โช
โช Do what we say
That's the way we kick it โช
โช You know what I mean
'Cause it's noisy
get wicked on ya โช
โช We're your first, last
and only line of defense โช
โช Against the worst scum
of the universe โช
โช So don't fear us, cheer us
If you ever get near us
don't jeer us โช
โช We're fearless M.I.B.s
Freezin' up all the flack โช
โช Who's that stand for
Men in black โช
โช The men in black โช
โช Let me see you just
bounce it with me โช
โช Just bounce with me
Just bounce it with me โช
โช Come on let me see you
just slide with me โช
โช Just slide with me
Just slide with me โช
โช Come on, let me see you
take a walk with me โช
โช Just walk it with me
Take a walk with me โช
โช Come on
Make your neck work โช
โช Now freeze โช
โช Ah-ha-oh-hey-oh โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Men in black โช
โช Galaxy defenders โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Men in black โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช All right, check it
Let me tell you this
in closing โช
โช I know we might seem imposing
but trust me โช
โช If we ever show in your
section, believe me
it's for your own protection โช
โช 'Cause we see things
that you need not see โช
โช And we be places
that you need not be โช
โช So go with your life
forget that Roswell craft โช
โช Show love to the black suit
'Cause that's the men in โช
โช That's the men in โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Here they come โช
โช Galaxy defenders โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Oh, here they come โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช Won't let you remember โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Oh, here they come โช
โช Galaxy defenders โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช Won't let you remember โช
โช Oh, here they come โช
โช Here they come โช
โช Won't let you remember โช
โช Galaxy defenders โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Oh, here they come โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช Won't let you remember โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช They won't
let you remember โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช Galaxy defenders โช
โช Here come
the men in black โช
โช They won't
let you remember โชโช