- Sure thing.
- Yeah, let me take your coat.
Uh, no. I have a better idea.
[shutter clicks]
WATCH ME.
VOILà.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
COLUMBIA PICTURES TELEVISION
♪ TELL ME WHY ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU LIKE I DO ♪
♪ TELL ME WHO ♪
♪ CAN STOP MY HEART
AS MUCH AS YOU ♪
♪ TELL ME
ALL YOUR SECRETS ♪
♪ AND I'LL TELL YOU
MOST OF MINE ♪
♪ THEY SAY
NOBODY'S PERFECT ♪
♪ WELL, THAT'S REALLY
TRUE THIS TIME ♪
♪ I DON'T HAVE THE ANSWERS,
I DON'T HAVE A PLAN ♪
♪ ALL I HAVE IS YOU ♪
♪ SO, DARLING,
HELP ME UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ WHAT WE DO ♪
♪ YOU CAN WHISPER
IN MY EAR ♪
♪ WHERE WE GO ♪
♪ WHO KNOWS WHAT HAPPENS
AFTER HERE? ♪
♪ LET'S TAKE
EACH OTHER'S HAND ♪
♪ AS WE JUMP
INTO THE FINAL FRONTIER ♪
♪ I'M MAD ABOUT YOU,
BABY ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ I'M MAD ABOUT YOU ♪♪
HOW LONG DID IT TAKE YOU
TO WRITE THIS PAPER?
HAVE YOU SEEN MY OTHER SHOE?
JUST PROMISE
I CAN SIT NEXT TO YOU
DURING THE TEST.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
O.K., I KNOW.
WHERE IN THE BEDROOM?
I UNDERSTAND.
THE KITCHEN PART
OF THE BEDROOM.
YOU KNOW,
LIKE, 8:00 OR 8:30.
IT'S NOT A DATE.
I JUST WANT YOU
TO MEET HER.
JUST DO ME ONE FAVOR.
WEAR THAT BEIGE SWEATER.
YOU'LL LOVE HER.
SHE'S THE MOST FUN PERSON
IN THE WORLD.
ISN'T FRAN FUN?
YES, SHE'S A CARNIVAL.
WHERE'S MY SHOE?
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT, THE BEDROOM
OR THE UPPER EAST SIDE?
YOU'RE NOT SHY.
YOU'RE THOUGHTFUL.
I AM THOUGHTFUL,
BUT I'M SHOELESS.
IF I WERE NICK,
YOU'D HELP ME
FIND MY SHOE.
NICK, I GOT TO GO.
I'LL MAKE A RESERVATION
FOR US SOMEPLACE TONIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU AT 8:00.
O.K.
SO WHERE DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD GO TONIGHT?
WHY ARE WE GOING?
'CAUSE IT'LL BE FUN.
WHY AM I GOING?
'CAUSE YOU'RE MY DATE.
LET YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
NICK BE YOUR DATE.
HE'S 25.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S A TURNOFF.
I FORGOT.
I GOT TO GO. BYE.
THAT'S IT?
WHAT--WHAT IS THIS?
LET'S HAVE SEX NOW.
THEN WE WOULDN'T
HAVE TO DO IT LATER.
HOW LONG WERE YOU TALKING
TO THIS GUY?
HE'S 25. COME ON.
I'LL DO ALL THE WORK.
WHERE WAS THIS
BIG ENTHUSIASM
WHEN I NEEDED YOU
TO FIND MY SHOE?
I WAS BUSY.
I REALLY DO
GOT TO GET
TO THIS MEETING.
WHAT MEETING?
IF I EXPLAIN IT,
IT WOULD TAKE
THAT MUCH LONGER.
DON'T DAWDLE
ON YOUR WAY HOME.
MOMMY WILL BE WAITING.
DID YOU JUST KILL IT.
NO, NOT YOUR MOTHER.
SO WHY YOU WANT
TO FILM MY GUY?
IS HE NOT THE FASTEST
SHORT-ORDER COOK
IN TOWN?
YES, HE IS.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN THIS MOVIE
COMES OUT,
EVERYBODY WILL SEE
YOUR RESTAURANT.
THEY'LL SEE YOU.
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE
TO SEE ME.
IT'S A DOCUMENTARY.
NOBODY WILL SEE IT.
MAYBE I DIDN'T
SELL THIS PROPERLY.
YOU'VE BEEN HERE
HOW MANY YEARS?
12.
HOW MANY TIMES
HAS SOMEBODY
COME IN HERE
AND OFFERED TO MAKE
A MOVIE ABOUT
YOUR RESTAURANT?
NEVER.
THERE YOU GO.
THINK ABOUT IT,
ALL RIGHT?
HAVE YOUR PEOPLE CALL ME.
I AM MY PEOPLE.
I WILL DEFINITELY--
WHAT IS THIS?
A NUMBER 12.
HE HEARD YOU SAY 12.
MAN, HE'S FAST.
ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
HEY!
HEY! HEY! HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DNG HERE?
I'M A BUSBOY.
I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU
THAT.
HOW DO I LOOK?
YOU LOOK LIKE A BUSBOY.
YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
ANTONIO, CLEAR 13.
YEAH, O.K.
ANTONIO?
YOU'RE ANTONIO NOW?
AND LOVING IT.
WOW!
DID I MISS A MEETING.
WEREN'T YOU, LIKE,
IN ALASKA OR SANTA FE?
PAUL, I WAS EVERYWHERE.
IT'S BEEN THE MOST
GLORIOUS 12 MONTHS
OF MY LIFE.
KNOW WHAT I DID
IN WISCONSIN?
SOMETHING WITH CHEESE.
I DON'T KNOW. WHAT?
MERCHANT MARINE.
LIVING ON A BARGE,
EATING SOUP
WITH MY HANDS,
AND I LOVED IT.
ALL MY LIFE
I'VE BEEN SO SHELTERED.
NOW I'VE SEEN THE WORLD.
I'VE FACED MY FEARS.
I'M A NEW MAN, PAUL.
HAVE YOU CALLED YOUR WIFE?
CAN'T DO THAT.
MARK.
DON'T YOU TELL FRAN
THAT I'M BACK.
I WON'T DO IT,
BUT COME ON.
YOU HAVEN'T SPOKEN IN,
WHAT, SIX MONTHS?
10.
10?
THE LONGER YOU WAIT,
THE HARDER
IT'S GOING TO BE.
NO, THESE STAY HERE.
I FOLLOWED HER
A FEW TIMES.
ONCE WHEN YOU WENT
TO SEE DAMN YANKEES.
LAST WEEK
YOU FOLLOWED US?
BOY, THAT
YOU GOTTA HAVE HEART
NUMBER.
I STOOD.
YOU DON'T EVEN STAND.
DID FRAN LIKE THE SHOW?
WOULD YOU CALL HER?
YES, I WILL. I WILL.
TUNA MELT.
FOR ME?
DID YOU SAY 10?
YEAH.
FOR YOU.
WHY ARE YOU MAD?
YOU KNOW WHY I'M MAD.
DON'T DO THAT.
MY MOTHER DOES THAT.
WHY ARE YOU MAD?
YOU LET ME WIN.
NOT EXACTLY.
WHY WOULDN'T I FEEL GOOD?
'CAUSE I'M A 33-YEAR-OLD
SINGLE MOM
BEING SET UP
WITH A 25-YEAR-OLD
COLLEGE KID?
HAVE A BEER.
I'M TELLING YOU
I THINK YOU'LL LIKE
THIS GUY.
I'M NOT WORRIED
ABOUT THAT.
HE'S
GOING TO LOVE YOU.
YOU THINK?
DEFINITELY.
WHAT ABOUT ME
DO YOU THINK HE'LL LIKE
SPECIFICALLY?
YOU'RE VULNERABLE
RIGHT NOW,
BUT GUYS LIKE THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
THIS IS
WHAT I'M WEARING.
WHY ARE YOU WEARING JEANS?
'CAUSE I'M HAVING
A GOOD ASS DAY.
YOU REALLY ARE.
YOU'RE NOT JUST
SAYING THAT?
NO.
TOWELS?
UH, THEY'RE RIGHT
NEXT TO THE SINK.
THIS WHAT YOU DO
WHEN I LEAVE?
AM I HAVING
A GOOD ASS DAY?
YES. VERY GOOD.
LISTEN.
IN A MILLION YEARS44
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHO I RAN INTO
THIS AFTERNOON.
YOU COULD START
NAMING NAMES NOW,
AND BY THE YEAR 3000
YOU'LL BE NO CLOSER
TO GUESSING
WHO I RAN INTO.
MARK.
MARK WHO?
WHAT MARK?
FRAN'S MARK.
HOW COULD IT BE
FRAN'S MARK?
NOBODY'S SEEN THE GUY
FOR OVER A YEAR.
YOU WANT TO GUESS?
GET SERIOUS.
O.K.
WHO'D YOU RUN INTO?
MARK.
NO! YOU SAW MARK?
I SAW HIM
NEAR PORT AUTHORITY.
HE'S A BUSBOY
IN SOME DIVE.
OH, MY GOD!
WHERE YOU GOING?
TO TELL FRAN.
I PROMISED WE WOULDN'T
SAY ANYTHING.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE
WHEN SHE FINDS OUT.
HE'S GONE FOR A YEAR,
AND I DON'T TELL HER?
STAY OUT OF THIS.
HOW DO I SIT THROUGH DINNER
AND NOT TELL HER?
TALK ABOUT ANY SUBJECT,
EXCEPT "MY HUSBAND
JUST SAW YOUR HUSBAND."
NO.
I KNOW I'LL CRACK.
NO. YOU'LL FLIRT
WITH NICK.
HE'S 25.
OH, YES.
THEN I FIGURED,
THE HELL WITH IT.
I DON'T NEED
ANOTHER MATH COURSE.
THAT IS HILARIOUS!
WHAT A GREAT STORY.
[FRAN]
A REALLY GOOD STORY.
THAT'S
SUCH A GOOD STORY.
CAN I GET ANOTHER DRINK?
URSULA?
HI.
OUR WAITRESS
SAYS HI.
TELL HER WE NEED
ANOTHER ROUND.
NO, WE'LL GET IT.
THANK YOU.
WHAT?
WHY THE LOOK?
YOU'RE VERY GIRLISH.
WHAT,
I'M BEING OBNOXIOUS?
YOU'RE LIKE
A LITTLE, HAPPY SEAL.
WE SHOULD GET
A COLORFUL BALL.
YOU COULD SPIN IT
ON YOUR NOSE.
I'M FLIRTING?
YES.
IT'S THAT OBVIOUS?
I'LL GIVE YOU $20
TO GO TO A MOVIE.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL HELP
GOOD-LOOKING BOY
WITH THE DRINKS.
PUT YOUR MONEY AWAY.
YOU'RE A STUDENT.
MY DAD'S LOADED.
I'LL CARRY THE DRINKS.
THANKS.
OH, BY THE WAY,
YOU KNOW THE LITTLE THING
WHERE YOU KEEP TOUCHING
MY WIFE?
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
WHOA!
WHEN YOU CARRY A DRINK,
YOU CAN'T THINK ABOUT IT,
OR YOU SPILL IT.
YOU'RE SO HELPFUL.
THANK YOU.
YEAH, I'M HERE IF YOU
EVER HAVE QUESTIONS.
OH, GOD.
WHAT?
HELLO, FRAN.
OH, GOD.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
I WAS BACK?
HOW WOULD I?
YOU DIDN'T TELL HER?
YOU TOLD ME NOT TO.
WHAT, YOU COULDN'T
SEE THROUGH THAT?
HOW COULD YOU
NOT TELL ME?
I DIDN'T WANT
TO RUIN YOUR DATE.
DATE?
THIS IS NICK.
HE'S IN GRAD SCHOOL
WITH JAMIE.
GREAT. I'M DR. DEVENOW,
FRAN'S HUSBAND.
I MADE 300 GRAND LAST YEAR.
NICE WORK.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M GREAT.
YOU GUYS HAVING FUN?
GOOD.
I WAS IN TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI.
FOR THREE WEEKS
I ATE ONLY OKRA.
I THOUGHT I SENT YOU
A POSTCARD.
BACK THEN I WAS STILL
RIPPING THEM UP.
YOU'RE T TAKING THIS
VERY WELL.
I REALLY AM.
HOW GREAT YOU LOOK.
DOESN'T SHE LOOK FANTASTIC?
SHE CERTAINLY DOES.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THIS IS T RIGHT.
YOU LOOK
10 YEARS YOUNGER.
I'M HAPPY.
AND I'M ACTUALLY
HAPPY FOR YOU.
GOOD FOR ME.
I'M GOING
TO GET GOING.
NO, DON'T BE SILLY.
WE'LL SPLIT SOME CALAMARI.
ARE THEY PUTTING ON
A SHOW?
THIS MUST BE SO HARD
FOR THEM.
WHEN SHE SLAPPED HIM,
THAT'S THE LAST THING
I UNDERSTOOD.
THEN I WAS A BRAKEMAN
FOR SOUTHERN PACIFIC.
FOR HOW LONG?
TILL I FELL OFF.
DIDN'T I GET A POSTCARD
FROM VIRGINIA?
WEST VIRGINIA.
I WAS A COAL MINER.
IN ABILENE
I MANUFACTURED BEEF JERKY
AND JERKY BY-PRODUCTS.
I AUDITIONED
FOR THE CLOWN SCHOOL
IN TALLAHASSEE.
ISN'T THAT THE HARVARD
OF CLOWN SCHOOLS?
YEAH.
INTERVIEW WENT GREAT.
WALKED RIGHT INTO A DOOR.
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
IT WAS.
YOU GUYS ARE KIDDING ME,
RIGHT?
WHAT?
WE SHOULD LET YOU GUYS
HASH THIS OUT.
NO, STAY. WE'RE
JUST CATCHING UP.
WE'RE
IN A GOOD PLACE.
HOW CAN YOU BE
IN A GOOD PLACE?
I DON'T GET IT.
WE'VE BOTH GROWN.
I FORGIVE HIM.
NEITHER OF YOU
ARE DEALING WITH THIS.
I THINK WE ARE.
JUST SO I KNOW I'M
ON THE SAME PLANET,
YOU--HE WALKED OUT
ON YOU.
I KNOW.
NO EXPLANATION.
IT'S WHO I WAS THEN.
MAYBE IT WAS
FOR THE BEST.
WHY DON'T WE
LEAVE YOU ALONE--
NO. THERE'S NOBODY
I'D RATHER BE HERE WITH
THAN YOU TWO.
AND NICK.
LOVE NICK.
YOU LOVE
YOUR WIFE'S DATE?
PLEASE, PAUL.
WE'RE NOT CHILDREN.
FRAN, ONE HOUR AGO
YOU SLAPPED HIM.
IT WAS
AN IMPULSE.
AND I FORGAVE HER.
AGAIN
THEY'RE FORGIVING.
WHY NOT?
YOU'RE SAYING
THERE'S NO CONSEQUENCE
TO HIS ACTION?
LOOK, PAUL,
NOBODY'S PERFECT.
I--
YOU KNOW,
SHE SLEPT WITH IRA.
LOVE IRA.
[POUNDS BELL]
COME ON,
PICK UP!
COME ON!
LET'S GO!
HE'S DEFINITELY
A LITTLE SLOWER TODAY.
IT'S TOO MUCH PRESSURE.
THE CAMERAS, LIGHTS.
WE'LL SHUT OFF
THE LIGHTS.
GIVE HIM A FEW MINUTES.
GO OVER THERE
AND SIT DOWN.
FINE.
AND DON'T BE
LOOKING AT HIM.
NO, I'M NOT
HERE, PAUL.
I'M GOING
TO CLEAN THIS OFF.
STOP CLEANING UP.
YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
PLEASE, PAUL,
IT'S MY JOB.
SESEE, WHY--
WHY WOULD SOMEBODY
PEEL THE LABEL OFF
A KETCHUP BOTTLE?
IT'S SO SENSELESS.
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
YOU THINK I DO?
LOOK,
IF HE CAME BACK
AFTER THREE MONTHS,
I WOULD HAVE
TAKEN HIM BACK.
IF HE CAME BACK
AFTER SIX MONTHS,
I'D HAVE KILLED HIM.
HE CAME BACK
AFTER A YEAR,
AND WE HAD DINNER...
GO FIGURE.
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
SO, HOW DOES THIS
WORK WITH YOU?
WHEN YOU'RE
TIRED OF THIS,
WHERE DO YOU GO?
WHEREVER LIFE TAKES ME.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
I'M ASKING A QUESTION.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
HOW DO YOU DO THIS?
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
I OPEN A ROAD ATLAS.
WHEREVER MY FINGER LANDS,
THAT'S WHERE I GO.
AND DO WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
EXPLORE. MEET PEOPLE.
HAVE FUN.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO JUST HAVE FUN?
WHEN I'M FINISHED
HAVING FUN,
I OPEN UP THE ROAD MAP--
BOOM!
POINT TO ANOTHER TOWN.
FREE...LIKE MY BROTHER
THE WIND.
SO, LIKE,
ON A WEEKDAY,
YOU GET UP, LIKE,
WHAT--7:00, 8:00?
YOU CAN'T IMAGINE
THE EXHILARATION.
THE FREEDOM OF LIVING
WITHOUT RESPONSIBILITY.
HERE, WATCH THIS.
HEY!
I QUIT.
YOU CAN'T QUIT.
O.K.
YOU GET THE GIST.
NICK SAID
YOU WOULDN'T GET IT.
YOU TALKED TO NICK?
THIS MORNING.
WE WENT OUT
FOR BREAKFAST.
A BREAKFAST DATE?
WE SHARED A MUFFIN.
YOU SEE? I TOLD YOU
YOU TWO WOULD HIT IT OFF.
HE KISSED ME.
NO!5340
HE DID.
HE DID NOT.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT IT'S LIKE
WHEN YOU WANT
TO KISS SOMEONE--
ONE OF YOU
MOVES CLOSER,
AND YOU KNOW IT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN,
BUT YOU'RE AFRAID
IT MIGHT NOT BE
AS GOOD AS
YOU IMAGINED?
AND WHEN IT HAPPENS,
IT'S EVEN BETTER
THAN YOU DREAMED?
NO.
SHE TALKS TO ME.
SHE SAYS, "NEXT TIME
YOU'RE IN ALBUQUERQUE,
YOU KNOW WHERE
TO REACH ME."
AND SHE'S HOW OLD?
PLEASE, PAUL.
AGE DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST TELL ME.
23.
OH!
HE DOESN'T KNOW ME,
SO EVERYTHING I SAY
IS NEW.
HE THINKS I'M FUNNY.
I FORGOT
I WAS FUNNY.
OF COURSE.
YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
I FORGOT!
AND THIS WOMAN
IN HAWAII?
KANAPALI OR HALEAKALA?
THE FIRST...PLACE.
GO AHEAD.
YOU'RE LIVING TOGETHER
ON THE BEACH?
YEP.
TWO WEEKS, THEN YOU SAY,
"THAT'S ENOUGH,"
AND YOU LEAVE THE BEACH?
YEP.-1 5
THAT'S O.K.?
YEP.
SHE'S NOT ANGRY?
NOPE.
SEE, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND THIS.
BUT YOU GET THE GIST?
I GET THE GIST.
IS HE A GOOD KISSER?
HE LOOKS LIKE
HE WOULD BE.
YEAH. HE HAS
REALLY YOUNG LIPS.
WELL, HE'S 25.
LAST TIME I WENT OUT
WITH A 2 25-YEAR-O,
I WAS 19.
THIS IS EVEN BETTER.
DOESN'T HE HAVE
GREAT HANDS?
I LOVE HIS HANDS.
THERE'S THIS CUBAN GUY
IN MY FRENCH CLASS--
WHY'S HE TAKING FRENCH?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE HAS BEAUTIFUL HANDS,
AND HIS ARMS--
I LOVE ARMS!
THEY'RE GORGEOUS.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
FORGET IT.
WHY?
I'M NOT INTRODUCING YOU
TO EVERY GUY AT SCHOOL.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU'LL DATE THEM,
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENS,
AND I'LL LIVE
VICARIOUSLY THROUGH YOU.
ISN'T THAT GOOD?
IT'S REALLY NOT.
IN ONE YEAR, THE GUY
HAS DONE EVERYTHING.
HE LIVED IN ALASKA,
HE HUNTED BIG ANIMALS,
HE SANG WITH MORMONS--
OW!
YOU GOT A 2x4 IN THERE.
HE RODE ACROSS TEXAS
IN A BOXCAR
WITH 200 HEAD OF CATTLE.
WHY WOULD HE RATHER BE
IN A BOXCAR WITH CATTLE
THAN WITH HIS WIFE?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT IF
THERE'S A GENUINE REASON,
I WOULDN'T WANT TO KNOW IT.
OW! OW!
I'M OVER HERE,
YOU PHONY.
AND THE THING
THAT REALLY UPSETS ME,
HE FEELS NO GUILT.
THAT UPSETS ME.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU NEED GUILT.
OTHERWISE PEOPLE WOULD
GO AND DO WHATEVER
MAKES THEM HAPPY,
AND I WON'T HAVE THAT.
SO, YOU'RE TELLING ME
THIS IS NEVER GOING
TO HAPPEN TO US?
0102 -1 5C405A40 30 P0102P0105P,
TO US?
NO. IMPOSSIBLE.
IF YOU EVER LEFT ME,
I'D FOLLOW YOU.
AND ME, I DON'T LIKE
GOING ANYWHERE.
HERE WE GO. GOT IT.
[SIGHS]
I WANT TO SEE IT.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S WHERE IT STARTED,
YOU DOPEY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO GET YOU A BAND-AID.
IF YOU WERE LIKE MARK
AND YOU COULD DO ANYTHING,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
ANYTHING ANYTHING?
YEAH.
I--TRULY?
I WOULD LIKE TO BE
A GOOD HUMOR MAN.
A GOOD HUMOR MAN?
YEAH.
I LOVE
THE SQUARE TRUCK,
THOSE THICK DOORS,
THE BELL,
THE LITTLE CHANGE-MAKER.
I LOVE EVERYTHING
ABOUT THAT JOB.
IF YOU COULD DO
WHAT MARK DID,
YOU WOULDN'T DO IT?
WELL, THERE'S A COST.
THE WAY I SEE IT,
I GOT TWO CHOICES--
1--I COULD HAVE
EVERYTHING IN THE WORLD
OR 2--I COULD HAVE YOU.
SO I...
GO WITH DOOR NUMBER 2.
THAT'S VERY SWEET.
YES. I'M
A VERY SWEET GUY.
WOULD YOU WANT
TO HAVE FRAN'S LIFE?
SHE'S DATING
YOUNG GUYS,
AND SHE HAS
ALL THIS FREEDOM.
DO YOU WANT THAT?
DON'T THINK ABOUT IT
A LONG TIME--
NO, NO, NO.
OF COURSE, NO.
I HEAR SOME YES
IN YOUR NO.
I HEARD MORE YES
I DIDN'T SAY NO.
YOU GAVE ME THAT
"I CHOOSE YOU" CRAP.
INTERESTING
HOW YOU ATTACK ME
AFTER I TAKE
THE SPLINTER OUT?
DOESN'T IT BOTHER YOU
THAT YOU'LL NEVER AGAIN
EXPERIENCE A FIRST KISS?
TRUE. YE.
IT BOTHERS ME
A LOT, YES.
DO YOU REMEMBER
OUR FIRST KISS?
UP AT YOUR
CHRISTMAS PARTY OFFICE.
I KNEW I LOVED YOU
WITH THAT KISS.
BEFORE OR AFTER?
DURING.
I WAS GOING TO
SAY DURING.
SEE?
NEITHER OF US WILL
EXPERIENCE A FIRST KISS
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
WELL, SO,
WE CAN HAVE IT
WITH EACH OTHER.
WE CAN'T.
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
I'M SAYING
YES, IT IS.
NO.
EXCUSE ME. HI.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
JAMIE.
JAMIE?
YOU'RE VERY CUTE,
JAMIE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO KISS ME?
YEAH, WHEN YOU'RE RIGHT,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M TELLING YOU.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
COLUMBIA PICTURES TELEVISION
ANYWHERE
IN THE WORLD?
ANYWHERE.
SEATTLE.
GREAT. WHAT DO WE DO
IN SEATTLE?
I WOULD FISH.
YOU COULD SELL
UMBRELLAS.
TRY AGAIN.
BURMA.
MMM...YOU GOT
TO GET SHOTS.
OOH.
NO, 'CAUSE I GOT FAMILY
RIGHT NEAR THERE.
I'VE GOT FAMILY THERE.
IN ISRAEL?
I DO.
YOU DO NOT.
DON'T ASSUME.